from the playful statements
by the web of rumours
Now you will get out
India will show more today
Monday to Friday
[music]
Research and evidence-based with
Ayurvedic Medicinal Purpose Patanjali Teeth
Best Ayurvedic for Kanti Dad
Toothpaste and Patanjali Kesh Kanti Advance New
Hair growth, hair fall and premature graying
protect from
[music]
My bands became flat amidst the ups and downs
The market is trading at a high of around 200 udhaar.
Pass 10 points below band then suffocating above
Song Gispal Kar Kar Rakh Neeche Ban
[music]
Song Gopi declines in the future
The government has no plans to increase the capital.
Clarification issued in the Income Tax Department
[music]
Gold jumped nearly $20 on a weaker dollar.
Silver near $2020 is one percent
Kutch oil rises to around ₹250,000 per litre
near the dollar
The government has reduced the windfall tax on turtle oil to zero.
Diesel price increased from ₹6400 per tonne
Export duty was reduced to zero
[music]
ICC Lombard defrauded 40% of profits
Veda today got a better result than expected with pace
Communications will result in
Ongoing
BML Land Assets to be listed today
A company made up of teams
We are having a cabinet meeting today at 10:30 am.
And today in Delhi, Prime Minister Narendra
You will meet someone else instead of Modi.
[music]
Hello everyone, welcome to Wednesday morning.
I am with you in fabric, Neha see
Let's take what we have in the midweek area.
If you have entered then what is the foreign signal?
types are available in our market today and
Cold start is this trick Nifty 20 by
Dove futures are also down 42 points
He is seen doing business and is
Talking about the future, this is also a red mark
I am showing weakness of 16-17 points.
If you look at the vacation marks, here
It has also begun and will also prove to be no exception.
If flats are not happening then negative trade
It is seen being formed here
Japanese weakness of almost half a percent
The market is down 108 points and the rest
All the markets that are open are completely flat.
You do business only in negative territory
We are seeing director trade
Commodity markets, especially bullion and
I have seen the rest divided into crude oil.
Molitis may turn out to be something like this
If it is showing signs of recovery then exactly
What happened in the session right now?
Our market share in international markets
Everyone understands what types of reasons there are.
My colleague Deepanshu is with me in the studio
We have been involved in two consecutive trading sessions.
Everyone is seeing that our markets are also cheap.
In a way, is this breeder late?
Is the market visible or is there really something like this?
There is data that is not getting clarity.
It will come later because the next major trigger
What is made for the market is fat for you.
The policy is going to come on May 3rd.
There is still time in between, you are watching.
There has been some reaction to the result, but that
Stock specific reactions are becoming more frequent
As far as the market is concerned, it appears that a
After the great rally that our market is seeing
Good before that in the US market
After that you were seen coming in a range
There's a little bit of consolidation going on and
US markets in the last four-five sessions
If I look at it, it's exactly the same thing happening.
Trades in a very narrow range
And you are almost flat band good
There has been a recovery and we saw it yesterday as well.
And off the recovery was good but almost
I live only in flats and diaries.
The trade is 100 points up 100 points
The same action below will take you through the last few days.
It is visible that there will be no change in this trade tomorrow also.
If I did not see it happening then after listening a little
They are definitely coming from the global market, but if
You see
Almost friends in the range of Rs 200
Show trades in progress End of here
You traded here and recovered 200 points.
Look, it's completely flat on the SAMP 500.
There was a slight increase, almost the same in illegitimate
The business was through De De and it started well.
After that a little decision was made in the market and then
through de de in a very small range you
Saw the business being done and it was completely flat
There was very slow business at closing time.
There were definitely three or four factors in the American bar.
Due to which stock specific action took place
A little bundle tomorrow hockey fall definitely here
Look at you, but two Fed members yesterday
Gave public speeches including James Bullets
You jeans whose speech we have often Fox
and both Fats members
Indications indicate that rates may rise further
So
Clearly, the recent three or four
There are indications regarding the feed policy.
indicating that there is another rate then you
Let's just assume it and then see what happens.
If it happens then go a little from there to the market
You saw the reaction coming, then now the result
If the season starts then you can stock there.
Banks are seeing specific action coming
Shares were once again in the Fox yesterday
Goldman Sachs and Bank of America both
Bank of America's results were seen coming in.
River results remained strong in stocks as well
You saw some positive action but
You can see the results of Goldman Sachs in front of you.
met who met who saw consumer side of.
Business is not as good as it used to be
The market had anticipated this and so have we.
Saw a decline of 1.5% in the city, which is good
Johnson & Johnson results were here
The company has revised its guidance and then
Netflix is ​​resulting in market band
If you have come later then through n when the market opened
When it happened, the stock was up only half a percent.
It was banned but today reactions are coming on this.
The result will be weaker than their slightest prediction
Yes, especially the figures that came are estimates.
remained weak and the second on password sharing
The more power the company was talking about
If strict action is not being taken at this time then perhaps
The markets would have been a little disappointed from there as well.
If you look at this today then the real reaction is Netflix
Let's see if we see you coming among the lions
How the market moves on this looks like Alpha
The lion is constantly showing weakness to both
There is some weakness nearby.
Because of this you will also see Morgan coming.
Stanley and Tesla, both of these giants
The results are going to come today, so on this also
One bank and one nearby will be important
Stocks related to IT and consumer sectors
So let's see how the market reacts to this.
and Fed's send book will also be issued
Now the seed book of Fit is available in 12 regional
The Federal Reserve has regional outlets.
From there they conduct economic surveys.
Manufacturing Services Employment
Regarding economic data, its complete
It is a mixture, it will be presented today, so let's see.
What do they have to say about future growth?
But something important about outlook
There are factors on which the market will keep an eye
You had a good birthday in Europe half the day before yesterday.
There was no problem there, the dollar index
It is back a bit after 2 days of rise.
Commodity market witnessed a range-bound rate
Crude oil is particularly large
There was no action and it traded around 8485.
China's economic data is seen doing this
I came in quite strong, so I got some support from there.
We definitely got a good one in Sony yesterday.
A rebound was seen back in 2020 at $2025
Gold in the range yesterday saw you coming
Silver action continues near $25
Because of China's data, we saw that
There was big action in base metals yesterday.
Both Aluminium and Nikhil are 2 months old.
Rebound in Agrimods is also at a height
Keep an eye on specialty coffee which is 6
At the height of the month, trades are being traded at this time.
There is buying in oils as well, so overall
There are some good signs of a stock
Specific reactions must have a result
But there has been no such big trigger yet.
I have not come for the market, but you have a big
If you see the reaction then go and trade directly.
is visible and no but news is
Actually, we expect some good news.
Our markets also react to this.
Thank you Deepu Puri will be seen in detail by the audience.
I came to put it in front of her and moved ahead of her.
First let us see what will happen tomorrow i.e. Tuesday.
How MP investors performed on 2018
So till now we were looking at it from its side.
There was a lot of shopping going on but yesterday
Begging of around Rs 811 crore was recorded.
and which domestic institutional applicants are slightly
He was behind a scam of ₹400 crore from his side.
If you have come up with the figures of purchases in the vicinity, then
The kind of signals we are getting are in the range of
Bound is Dare's
Amidst all this, today in our market you will find
What did you have to do, we will talk about our news.
have joined us
[music]
From two trading sessions in the same morning we have one
Are you looking for healthy business like this?
Will we still have fun in the mood today or will we get something today?
Strength signals can be obtained
And I am creating a very simple level.
Is
175007575 Strong support John is easily
It is not going to break above 17750
If he still doesn't seem to be coming, then remember him.
If you look at it from the beginning, you can get support before rent.
Whatever is between ₹500-600 can be easily purchased.
If you call the bank then there will be weakness
Signals will come when 40 goes below 500
If you are someone above from there then there
The comfort zone is very high and it will be available from today
If till today for banking or internet
If you look at the support then it is from 41800 to 42000.
Will remain in range and from the palace on the subsistence
Minor resistance near ₹542,000 and ₹600
If you do it then come out with good speed.
And you can make it possible
Like Kali, today again another change is what you
We will see
Fox would be better
too much udder
ok no sir
What range keeps our audience watching?
17500 to ₹575 support range to follow
That will prove to be a boost for Nifty.
Blockage it may jail near 17825 bank
Nifty 41842000 a strong support there
appears to be bent and above 42 600
I can see this going on clearly sir
has said that cash market stocks are midcap
There are space companies, they cough here
There will be trading and stock specific action
You have to do it Fox and we are going to do the same.
We are in the stock sector based on the news.
The action will be seen with full details, Nupur is with us.
Which numbers are reported together?
First tell me if you have come because the numbers
It's the season of plus triggers and news
But where to stay action stock specific
So good morning first of all
Let's start with the triggers.
Communication
The results of Alok Industries will be seen coming.
Is the listing of land in Mumbai going to happen today?
If we talk about global surface, then here 50%
IPO login will end today 30
The IPL log in of the day ended today.
If it is seen happening then this stock will also be in Fox
Shipping Corporation of India is going to stay
Where the change in price band is 20% today
Above 5% increased to 20%
So you are keeping an eye on this stock today.
Apple CEO Tim Cook too today
He is going to meet Prime Minister Modi
This event should also be kept under watch in Delhi.
There are going to be cabinet meetings as well.
10:30 But whether CCE is there or not, here
If seen from the global perspective, Europe will also be under scrutiny.
And data from the UK is due in March.
The market conditions here also vary during the month of
If we start with the result, we will see
First ICC Lombard where Joe
The results of the waterfall are much greater than Hanuman.
Talking about the net premium, butter was seen coming
You are up 12% compared to last year
Butter should be shown as profitable even beyond expectations.
40 you will see growth of Expand fibers
Look, Andaman has maintained 27%.
Sarees constituted 31% and also those made of combined fibres.
Talking about the expectation of 108%
I saw 104% coming from the front and was quite positive.
ICC Lombard's numbers are visible
Tata Coffee in Cash where revenue is 10%
It came in more than that but with a lower profit
So you will see a 5% reduction there.
Margins decline by 200 basis points
News of the decline from 17% to around 15% was seen.
I first look at you and
ONGC Reliance Marketing Company
Industries like Oil India MRPL
Some news related to the topic of tax came.
See where the notification of new rates is available.
The government has issued domestic
on crude production
64%
If you have invested, then this stock will remain in focus today.
There are President's States where
The subsidy of subsidiary Prestige Company
has bought 51% stake in it
This transaction is worth approximately Rs 66 crore.
has been done to Piramal Pharma where
Positive news came from USFD NA company
In the facility of K, its IAIR
The report has been released, so this is what is written here.
The inspection was over, Jazz.
Life Sciences where the market is worth Rs 15 crore
A company having
Approval has been received for this medicine.
So positive music, this is also for the company.
Pidilite Industries where the company
Key Basic Address to Luck with a Car
Although the amount has not been disclosed,
With this the company upgrades its technology
If she is going to do it then it is positive news
Bachpan Enterprises for Pidilite as well
Where again a quarter form
Your stake is only larger than the previous 2.5%
The share was increased to about 3%
And lastly Tata Investment where Tata
Investment where news is published
Tata Sun is a Taiwanese company and
Acquisition of Western's Bengaluru plant
Tax power is 5000 crores, this is how it was done
If needed, it will be in Fox
Fox and his strength in select stocks today
You will definitely get some earning in this sector.
Could you please thank Nupur for the complete details?
I would have killed myself to put it in front of the audience
What are the experts in the market now?
Opinion is being formed on which sector stock
He seems to be talking about everything
Mehul of shares not eligible to
Kothari joins us on the show now
Are
A dare trade we're looking for broder
Talk of Nifty Bank Nifty in the market
But do you think buyers are upwards?
What if there's a strategy to adopt today?
will be
[music]
Pressure will go to Aldo a little bit of recovery
Yes but here profit booking sir we need
Due to this, the Bank Nifty is
Put Option of 42000
[music]
Will have a stop loss of 50 up to 250
Nifty seems to be hitting the target
I am in a position right now or are you waiting right now?
would like to
Come see Neha ji, the one in Nifty
Breakout of the breakout channel
The theoretical target is very big but
How is it, I am talking about upset.
But even before this, a similar line was seen in February
had taken up which had failed and after that
We saw a low of 16800 so here I
I will wait and watch Nifty for a while.
17500 is a lot of Krishna support
For me it is 17500 if there is a break
So the breakout that I talked about
Breakout night will happen and then we'll be back again.
Will be lost in preparing for new downsides
17500 is such a level in the market where
All loans should have a stop loss like this
I think the prefix is ​​obviously ₹17801
There was Hardaul, after that there were 18000 who
This is a psychological level, worth 200 points.
The range is very strong hurdles
It will be proved that Supply John is in upset.
This level is 17500 and below.
The level is
We will keep an eye on the level and from there its break
The connection will appear as a download here for now.
He is the support, he is well headed, so you bank
Whoever focuses on Nifty will give you his point.
Here is advice to take
Where do you see stock specific action?
Hey Mehul ji, today you seem to be earning money.
Is
First stop is at Bajaj Auto Bajaj Auto
There is a nice break and we rally
Well in the last two weeks now he's been a little
Ready for huge profit booking
If so, then 4160
Buying the put option of 4160
I would recommend it to be around ₹35, the rate is ₹35
There is a stop loss of ₹20 and
This is our first target of Rs 60.
The second pick is MFL very
A good special collection has been strong
I have taken support and I think Song Fool
If you are preparing for bank then keep it in cash.
We have to buy ₹650 and the remaining amount is ₹45.
Stop loss is closed at the same point in the range
Its price will be ₹620 and if it is in position then
The gate will remain
Target will be Rs 60 for S Excel 650
Have to take around ₹620 stock will remain plus
And the target will be 700 and let's go right to this
Let me repeat it for the audience
Get ₹160 off on Bajaj Auto 4160
I have to take it at 35
Stop loss of 20 and target of 60.
You can find it here and S Excel here
Near 650 you have to enter 620
Stop low target up to 700 is given to you here.
Banta will be seen, well tell me this, we
Yesterday's session saw Pharma Healthcare
Space has been a bit beige and that's why
Because we're seeing cases that are one
If the bar appears to be increasing again,
It appears to have fundamental support.
He is giving me this paste, please tell me now.
There's a stock you like on the charts.
has been a
Space has been going on for a long time, actually.
A little bit of it from last month
We have seen the performance, so the specific
From pharma stocks to Biocon
Sir Doctor Glenmark is the best among all
A special rally has been held, I think a little
Many rallies have not yet come, which
They say that lab people have a hobby.
Diagnostic center, anyway, has no stock.
As the red ruined Metropolis
Once all this is done, I will give you a little traction.
If you can see then Metropolis is a
counter that we're seeing so far
There is no confirmation but it is after 1300
I think you're straightening it up
There will be a slight bounce and it will go up to 1400.
level in which it can be seen
metropolis that we have
On the radar and looking something in the IT space
because after some time we had
Dekha ko four JM face kal take these powerful
The performance was called It Here You Continue
We will not be able to speak level specific
Because it's a little volatile.
The entire sector, I think yes.
After the fall in Infosys
There is a little bit of call bike uplaj but
[music]
Overall long period of time means three-four
If we talk about month or 6 months then that IT
The sector is not looking that good to me.
It seems that there is still a little bit of Dr. Side
If there is a child in them then there is butter that a little weight
And watch it, there is a confirmed signal in it.
Do it only when you get the chance and for a very short term.
I have a bike for this if any brother also does it 2 4%
If you get upset then book it there.
I should take it okay let's go thank you so match Mehul
Yes, to tell us to join us.
What exactly is the strategy here?
If you want to adopt in the sector then of course Pharma
Companies in the lab space take on the healthcare space
Keep an eye on Metropolis today's recommendation
So there is also a little bit of IT space.
You should keep the ups and downs in mind while walking.
It will happen that you will be a little cautious in this also.
So you get earning opportunities in a short period of time.
Where can I get Quietus on the face?
We have come to know that there are opportunities to earn money.
But the market also has a lot of action in it.
We can see it, we will talk about it all.
Motilal Oswal present its Amit with us
Amit has joined the directing team, we are watching.
Be it energy or bullion
Yes Sony, will you start with silver, please tell me
If you were to adopt a strategy today, what would it be?
So that good morning yes see yesterday we had dollars
Golden is due to collection in the index
Silver both coming in open bag
We saw that for the first two sessions we continuously
The fall was good so I think this
This is a flower bag and it will continue to be a bank in gold.
The advice would be ₹60000 when the tip is around 300
If found, the bank's power is in oxide
We are looking at targets up to around 6000-800.
If we talk about silver, we will get the same
Let's see closing above 75000.
It seems that when we get around 74700
So you will get the buying opportunity and now
Around 75 heads on the side ranging from 700 to 76000
We will see you again
Let me repeat the silver which is present
The contract is near 60000300, take it
6000050 will have a stop loss of 6000050
Silver is seen rising up to 60000800
Also in silver
Buying is divided near 74700
Level up to 7576000 is visible on the upside
And in that you have a stop loss of Rs 74100.
It is good to use it, what is there in crude oil
It should be done exactly near 84 85
Because there is data from both sides here.
Supporters and brakers
What to do too
After that we have seen the crude oil story
I have seen the story getting a little better and tomorrow
After the initial decline in the session
We
Gave a great closing
Closing above 60 is given on sex.
I believe that 6600 is also limited.
There is support and there is the power of leadership.
Is
[music]
The entry will be a buy stop loss of 6540
And target up to 6730 in crude oil
The base metal will look good, of course it will react
Copper above 9000 based on China data
The aluminum has been removed for two months.
If you have highsper then you are comfortable with metal
I'm in shopping now
We are seeing a lot of bargain hunting.
After the lower range of Meena and tomorrow Aloe Vera
I was out of age
I believe the performance will continue here.
MCX buy near 211
Shakti is aiming for 216 and straight
If it is necessary to take a stop of 208
Will do some good shopping in aluminum
Come back, it also entered the international market.
Shown near 200 11 for target of 216
Best entry Bunty hai thank you so match Amit
Yes, to tell us to join us.
What should I do in Moti Market today?
Let's talk about investment again.
of reports
[music]
Ashish join us for complete details.
Ashish, have you finished, tell me in the morning?
After the report, you should buy a car.
Even after getting good results, you should keep looking at the target.
The price has been cut from Rs 1500 to Rs 1500.
Made it 1400 although Mogini is exactly 1400
GP maintains target at Rs.
Morgan gave a rating of Neutral and
He also reduced the target from 1250 to 1500.
Day they have made it 1107 so here
You'll put up against Fox, who's got fridges and all that.
If you see it, keep your shopping routines intact.
The target has been changed from 1620 to 1560
I have kept the perform creation inside and
Highest Acquire on ICC Lombard
It is being seen because 965 means 1131
Closing is current, giving target of 995
Below market price, apart from this, yesterday
India, if you look here also, in the last
You will get to see some good action in both.
I have got it in a government company, anyway it is just
So GP Morgan is overweight here.
Training
There has been an increase but no significant
You see, it hasn't increased
You should have given it, now it has been increased to ₹290
Although calculated from the current market price
The website is still here
Because Titan is closing at 232 here.
We also have to keep Fox because tomorrow we will be like this
Reporter from Make these purchases and which targets
Increased from 3000 to 3150
2578 which is tomorrow's closing
The Fires are watching here and so are we.
It will be there because there will be plenty of action here.
Thank you Ashish, that complete detail is for the audience.
Power with IC for front lay
This is how we wrap up breakfast
But stay tuned to Zee Business.
After this we will bring you Traders Diary which will help you in
See you today please strong trading
[music]
Remove chemicals, turmeric, sandalwood
The biggest name of trust but style
Absolutely common man whose experience and understanding
Even the giants salute in easy language only profits
Everyone is talking about the country
[music]
Do you trade in the stock market?
Isn't it true, every morning at 7:30 am on Zee Business
You will get everything that traders need every day.
Daily Cash Future Option Index is required
Technical picks on the strength of news lion and
Nothing for investors, right?
A great investment pick and a great one
Funda Pick also means daily dose of trading
Get on Business every day at 7:30 am
Only in Trader's Diary
will come out
A luxurious and flawless journey, the number one in the market
Leader
The biggest name of trust but style
Absolutely common man whose experience and understanding
Even the giants salute in easy language only profits
Everyone is talking about the country
Your trusted business news for 16 years
Channel Zee Business your benefit
Do you trade in the stock market?
from the storm of
from the maelstrom of information
from the playful statements
by the web of rumours
Now you will get out
Jeep to showcase more India 360 from Monday
Friday evening at 7:56 p.m.
A wonderful and flawless journey
The number one market leader
The most trusted name
[music]
Prevent whitening
America
[music]
HDFC ₹1700 Near Doubt Features 60 Points
The lower body fell by 75 points.
The government has no intention of increasing capital gains tax.
The Income Tax Department has issued a scheme, not a plan.
Cleanliness is very important on Zee Business news.
Gold jumps nearly $20 on weak dollar
Silver rose 1% to $25 near
Kutch oil near $85
[music]
The government has imposed a windfall tax on oil.
more than zero
₹6400 per turn exported on diesel
Duty reduced to zero
ICC Lombard name moves 40% into profit
I have presented it with Hanuman, today I have got good results
Tata Communications results in futures
Will be watching
Listing today became a demerger of BML
The company is
So hello to you in Traders Diary
Welcome to the midweek session and overall G
The mood and atmosphere today is quite pleasant.
India is a country where there is a lack of news and numbers too.
Not much today, not that much tomorrow either.
were so stop have taken some absolutely some
So I have taken stock and in this matter
There was a continuous competition going on in
If any news comes, who will be the first to lie down?
If there is any ace then even if you get some news
I have seen him but I will cut him completely.
will play along with this which you will get if you
Tell us how you think the global outlook is.
Global, if you from this time I, if you tomorrow
or what is visible today
What kind of atmosphere is visible there too?
It is cheap whether you are talking about American markets
and its indications give us exact
You are also seen coming on Nifty
Showing almost flat sir registry
Here's a breakdown of numbers since 1920.
Currently, business is seen taking place and two
If you look at Jones, he turned out to be a little like this.
C-shopping has also been seen returning here but
Largely the sentiment is like flats
Show the band happening, look at the other side
There was a fall like this above and that fall
If there is some tax during the whole day then tax
Shares are a huge support there right now.
17 and Europe is not seen coming
And if you look at the market,
From there also the trend is more positive
No, although you will see in tomorrow's session.
So, a little bit of every mark in all the three indices
I was seen doing business
Slightly better than the European market
There are signs but now the treatment also has to be seen.
The fee figures will be announced in tomorrow's session.
Approximately Rs 810-812 crore was seen here.
Faiz had sold in the cash market
There was no other story, no story, I had expectations
So it seems that what China is doing here tomorrow
GDP data came in, it was estimated at 4% 4:30
percent of Q1 GDP comes, he gave
So it may happen that Fis puts India in the middle
Growing our positions here in China
Can be seen in the future
Because we were just looking at it
For the last two-three months, you have seen China reopening.
Story or story can be a big positive
of Global Institutional Investors
A major factor for the future appears to be emerging
I will have to take it out and see the butt because I am in the mood
India's story is also quite interesting and if
If Fiji is making a mistake, we will have to see that
Here's how much bigger Jens will be in the future.
You can take it but the scenario remains the same.
that Almstry is being sold from the global market
The mood is not very volatile
The sessions that are earning heavy are the next ones.
Lalji is seen starting from the week
Will come but this week also keep in mind that
Reliance numbers are also coming.
Let's see what its impact is, Pari.
How Reliance numbers are affecting the entire market today
How do I get over and how do I feel about the mood and atmosphere, but
In a way, the scenario is still so
Tell us how many bets you placed on your purchase and
Which is the first cash stock you choose?
He should also tell the viewers to see who is the best
The big news if you look at today is that Involt
Tax on the basis of this, if you look at it then write
Yes, I mean there is a put option and I have taken Excel.
You will see the rest overall, everything else is bye now.
First of all, if we talk about category then it
what stock what stock what I stock
He has taken it, it is his now
Listing of BML Land Assets
If listing is due
So overall when you look at it, if always
Properties They also have a plant bank and
If you look at their results in Q1
When the result came, its page
At number 6 he has his land
The value mentioned there is approximately 100600
It is around crores but the share value if you
If we calculate it then it will be around 300.
comes and if the current prices are visible then
She almost didn't have you around to sleep sex
around what has been seen since around 1993
If you see it, the discount is approximately 70%
So if you have bomb land assets, if you
The listing also seems to be getting a little better.
If it is seen going above ₹250 then it may be
Let's see if momentum comes here too.
You saw a good moment coming yesterday too.
That's why we buy properties from this
I will make a profit of 96 and keep this top loss at 92.
Absolutely
Listing of land assets is about to take place
Keeping this in mind, we
Recommended purchases for properties here
It is being prepared from Armaan's side, come towards me
From how in the comments is Mon Dis's actually tomorrow
The company has given the news that one of their
There is a subsidiary there, there is a capacity
has expanded in Karnataka and in that
which are commercial operations
If its production has started then
Commercial Production
It has been said in the company that it will be seen coming
They will be seen to benefit greatly from it.
Anyway, you look at the counters, these counters
Look, there has been a continuous upward momentum.
And tweeting almost 160 times.
So, it turned out to be much more spectacular than the stars.
The purchases are shown broken down here and
Story, no story, even in tomorrow's session
There has been some momentum and it is still going on today.
It is as it is because the impact of the news today
You can also find the answer to this.
So here are the good opportunities to buy.
You should target 165, you should target 156
stock can let's move on and
Here you can see in the derivatives space we have
Let's talk about which stops we have chosen.
First up is the Features category from my side.
JSW Steel counter is now in
I have been in the metal space for the last two-three weeks.
Continuous
I told you about the character on April 11th.
Hindalco's counter and since then you
Look at the kind of momentum that's distributed there.
I have seen it and now I feel that the
There are steel counters there too you will get speed.
There is power to look forward because
Likely in the clear American market
There is also metal a little outside
He was seen doing this in yesterday's session also.
Up to 1 1/2 to 2% of the gain was distributed there.
If it was good then JSW Steel is doing this
Keeping this in mind, you should consider purchasing
There can be good opportunities to do so, so of 740
Keep your target here also at 712
Plus, if we talk specifically about metal, see
If we talk only about steel then
If the story of China is good then
You will see almost the story in all the metal
So 50% of the production also belongs to them.
And if there is a little bit of consumption there
If the studio is good then the rest of the sarees
For the company, even if there is a 10% loss,
If it is a very big thing then definitely whatever
Your star is what you keep giving
There are plenty of bright futures that I've
The one that has been sold is Reliance, now its region
what is it because if you have heard it
Watch Joe Simple on Domestic Production
64% of the tax is now levied
So if you look at the logic here, if
If you see, this is a negative news here.
It is for them that I am on the star of this
I will also give you another stock accordingly.
Reliance has to sell its future.
If you keep the target and keep this topless then 375
If I had done this and similar pay options
The option you are buying is ONGC.
There is a similar asterisk here also, as soon as
If you think the voltage is good
Show you growing bigger than you were before
After that you come to 64%.
It was seen here that this is also for them if you
If you see, then negative story is happening.
ONGC is facing negative tax due to this
Also, I will buy Put option for 160 which is 1.4
You are getting around, target will be 1.85
and keep a stop loss of exactly 1.25
So let's focus on Reliance and ONGC, these two outer ones.
Arpan's eyes are fixed on Imphal in the same way
Tax on crude oil is back on the rise
If you can see any story then this is not a story here
It is possible that you may have to sell here.
If you see it, let's move forward with it.
And I have selected the stock options category.
The way ICC Lombard's numbers came in
Yes, they're looking pretty good, especially now.
In terms of profit, it is 40%
Growth is here while the street's
Estimates and our estimates are also around 340 crores.
The company had recorded a profit of Rs 437 crore.
Has a premium in the health segment
The growth has been good and I am happy with the results.
When I was checking, the commissioner in it
Their line item is specifically total expense.
In that case, it would have gone straight from 160 crores to 90 crores.
Let us show what happened to Commissioner Plus Brokerage.
If it is a line item, then clear cut indications are given.
That the expenses here have reduced.
The benefit of this is coming to their bottom line.
If it has been seen then due to this such things are seen here
Shop on Fox and go online
The premium was further increased to Rs 1140 by around 12:30.
Tomorrow option is available here at 28 to buy
Do it for the target of Rs 41 and Rs 20
Your stop will come here, so let's go to options
Degree is complete, let's move ahead with technology.
In terms of pick, from our stock, it has
First up from me tomorrow is ABFRL
That is Aditya Birla Fashion and Retail.
Here I am getting the feeling that the tax sector
Showing continued weakness and is still in the long term
You can see the chart of 3 months and 6 months here
But Continuous Dr. Train gives you both
Coming to the time period here
I have seen you friends, let me give you the week's outer
It is happening and today if again in the market
If there is a sell-off, it may happen that
The long unwinding here is continuous Ibe
It is happening in FRL and would have continued even today.
It was seen in the red mark in yesterday's session as well
There was a band, there is a sell-off opinion in the tax sector
But only for the target of Rs 218 and which
You have to make a stoppage at the hair site.
This technopic of mine will cost Rs 228.
Look at the Techno Pick from the side if you are talking about
If I do it then I will do it on the pay chart.
compatible is feeling good that's because you
Overall, if you look at the chart, its chart
You will see what is interesting
If you look at it for a while,
This is growth, this momentum that has come, you
Well written, if you look tomorrow also, almost
You saw a sharp eye of around 2%
So overall, if you look at it from space, this
The target you have to keep is 125 and
The stop loss is to be kept at 120 9.5 because if
You see, technically, this is sounding to you.
Now it is time to fund out fundamental stocks.
Fundamentals taken according to the funda
That is ICC Prudential, see the overall
If you are looking to buy this stock or this space
Why not talk about this space story of time?
for just one year for two years
No, it is for a long time, the reason for this is that
If you are some points which are
Sector wise, only this company has
Not sector specific
This is necessary if you want to avail sum assured today.
Percentage of GDP will see how much percentage
of GDP, if you look at that
Talking about the insurance space, I am Life
In the insurance space, about 22%
Our country's comes approximately if you look at that
If you see, it comes for 250%, this will be on one side.
Another way to look at the protection gap is
How much protection do we need and what
How much difference is there already, approximately that is our
If you look at the country, it is about 83%
comes around while Indonesia while there
But his score is also 76%, which is even lower than the average.
There is a lot that you are forgiven for in this space.
Will grow well
If you see something in the text,
According to this, definitely if you see the news
It was because of its impact that this happened, it appears that
There is a little interest in the sector.
When you see it getting loose then you can use this thing in your life.
Insurance policies you have or are purchasing
These are long term purchases only.
Obviously it is not done to save tax.
If specifically it is on a long star
If you look at it, this compatibility is about space.
Well, you get momentum in the company.
It will be seen that for the long term I
I am giving the duration for only one year but
This strong thing that keeps you going
should be kept in the portfolio and every fall
I should send you a little bit here.
The target will be 550 and the duration will be one.
Fundamentally, this is the proof for me.
Liked it Kushal what do you like
See here Armaan from my side Funda Pic
So I kept seeing this over and over again,
Mahindra and Mahindra bring this to you in a big way
Fox you should walk back to what
I feel that the fall was never there, but now it is happening.
The doubtside risk story is no longer a story.
Its bottom has been made and for the future
Growth triggers, they look amazing
The company has also said that it is being seen
that the portfolio that is there by 2027
About 20 to 30% of it, that is, of the entire
20 to 30% across passenger vehicles
He will be seen getting electric
The XUV400 was also launched and
Great response to them there already
It has been seen to match and anyway we
You know the history that Mahindra and
Mahindra as a pioneer here
When he launched his own
Did the initials Ila a think of 2010 or
The car that he had in 2012 has arrived.
It was visible but obviously that time was so
The adoption was not as fast as it was mature.
It could have been on the page but like Tata Motors
He has taken the lead now, this could be possible.
That Mahindra is the second best Mahindra
Bring out your computer and get your market shares.
To increase further now
Their current portfolio is not that large.
But if these people capitalized on this thing
And the management is also like the big Fox ji now.
The statement comes from that it is visible in 2017
It is not that far, I think there is a gap of 4 years.
And the story is the scenario that is being created now.
As many auto component players as possible
He is also on his own and on his kit
His portfolio size seems to be increasing.
has been a
I heard that you like B L W a lot.
I know so if you have two stocks that you
If you want to keep the best in these spaces then
Who else but the gold BMW
We will keep the same in it, Mahindra and
I think Mahindra is the first Tata.
I have a motor but I love Eminem now.
I like it more because the way
His execution has been particularly
TV obviously in the portfolio going forward
One is the transmission thing and if Mahindra
And Mahindra capitalized on that too.
There is some competition on the designing front.
They too have not had any historical history.
in the portfolio which in today's session
The biggest preferred demand of consumers is
So there is a huge waiting period for that.
I'm constantly watching what's going on here.
and Mahindra and Mahindra I think their
Whatever is the most portable right now, it is already there.
This is the scenario of waiting for six to eight months.
Mahindra and Mahindra brings you here
Fox do how along with it Joe Asterisk
Eminem is seen coming from him
You will also get a big Fox at Tata Motors.
So Eminem by my side
Good opportunities to buy N Fundep ahead
I can become one and I am going to lose it in the next 1 year.
The target of 1400 is for you to move forward.
We should choose the fundamentals and move ahead. Let's move forward.
We are ahead and our next category is
Let's discuss IPL.
Space has stock from my side
Britannia counter is quite different from both.
I was on retirement but now I have some courage
I got the shoe because it was
If you look at the bridge of Britannia
Portfolio with biscuits is pan oil par ji
kind of decline in the last couple of years we've
Aai Hui is good, she is a great support and
The consumption story is basically the FMCG space
If you look at me, it is moving forward with strength
Show growing tomorrow you will see Nestly
Almost 3:30 such a big counter of the day before yesterday
Despite being three 3:30 the day before yesterday
If the games are shown then they are worth a bit.
You can appreciate the scenario here.
It is being made for them and Britannia gives me
It's been here for a long time now
Definitely Nivedita can do fundamentals
No problem and whatever I need for the future
It is being said that the next 12 minas will be here.
At least 10 to 15% of the games in 4900
For targets of Rs. 10000, you can visit Britannia
Shopping is power, see Britain
Speaking of, when the minute status continues to play
Had started in those few both if you
See her time Britannia my bone of
D stock was there, targets were also achieved there
Then after that now Kushal took him forward and metal
are handling
Definitely and generally, if you just look at
If you talk about consumption space in this basic way
If we talk about elections then
Talking about her period, there
If you see consumption in general, it will be a good relief.
If it is there then it is definitely good butter as per that.
IPL stock is a good company
The stock I like is Prestige
State Project Now here I will tell you
I will tell you some things which you will learn from a master.
There is one in presentation and installation, so their
How many upcoming projects are there? Approximately 43
What is the area of ​​upcoming projects? 93
billion square feet yet if you talk
If so, how many projects have they completed?
are doing 278 what was its area yesterday 65
million square feet means more than half
Joe's upcoming projects are 9
If you look at the press release of the monastery, you
Mr. Presentation who looked to be getting results
were the highest you saw the highest sales
The collection shows you everything going great
If you see 81% of the inventory that is there now
If in the last 12 mins what they launched
The tax is 81% of the inventory that is there.
You will see that TV is quite good.
See the trust of institutions here
If it is around 30-31%, then such a company's
If you look at it, its brand value is quite high.
It's great where you have robbers
Outlook seems to be coming because the new
There are projects, you will also get space there.
You have a great momentum in
It was coming from consumers and was going on.
and such a brand where if you see
The constant demand for new projects
There must be some very good robots going on there.
and if you want compatibility then
If you look at good compatibility
If the valuation is available there then
Prestige Strat Project which is a
It makes a good bed and has a long duration.
Will keep 12 Meena and target five
Absolutely desire and
This is not a premium story in the state space.
The story is believed to be like his
projects come keeping that in mind
Happened here regarding Prestige Status
Positivity is distributed and so is the way
Rates have paused and demand has been consistent.
It is flooding, what is happening to you?
for real estate because you are real estate
If you track what your inclination is
But I would like to know that traders
Next in the diary is I also take some stock
No no look I can give you maybe
We used this to see if you could spend one or two years
It was a year ago, when
Not even a year ago if you look at all these
Companies that released the Bangalore report
At that time I had also told you one thing through my link.
You can buy f5 22 carat sarees from these companies.
Gold report of all companies is available
Everyone said one thing which is body rest.
I am thinking that this is a big bicycle
The cycle that was in real estate
Whatever it is, it seems to be coming back and this is a
Not the company, you are an offer from any company.
Look at the reality by picking up any company.
Look, all the big companies were saying one thing in common.
And now it's red pose and like red pose
If it happened then that real estate one of D just like that
There was a sector where you would see a lot of daylight.
Excellent
It continued and you saw it before that too.
This was however if you opt for some premium
Talking about projects, those which
Even after getting jealous of the tax advantage, Rs 30
It happened in March but whatever little I
I have also spoken to many brokers.
giving perspective that the real estate
There is a lover and there is real estate there
The demand is great and there is a good
If there is demand, then real estate should be sold accordingly.
So I'm quite a police in comparison now.
We go by the news as per the news.
I have taken stock that is Enterprises
Because as you look at Q4
You will get continuous updates on Lion Only.
Congratulation is being shared here
How much does it cost, congratulations and share
They increased it from 2.5% to about 3%.
I have talked only about this cotton
Don't do it if you see that in this photo
Take it, it is difficult if you total number of
If you see, that too will be more than 50, you will get approximately
I have seen you turning 60, even before that if you
See, it was 2.21 in June and then the following September
in 2.2
If you look at it now, it would be around 3%.
If you look at it, there is nothing like it there.
Told that where we are constantly thinking about it
I think this thing is causing us problems.
If they are doing that, then some such stocks
Where if he does it little by little
If you are increasing your stake then there you will
Compatibility becomes a bit of a convention
So according to this news, welfare
Enterprises will target to buy
Will keep a stop of 140
It appears to be buying from its side
Keeping this in mind, buy here today
You can do this on the news, I have stock from my side
Now you can see Riders Life Science here
But news has come that he has been selected in the final
Approval received USFDSA Studial
Now Annual for Trans Dermal System
If you look at the sales of this medicine,
Not very big in America
It is worth around Rs 15 crore but like pharma
Space is in full momentum tomorrow as well.
You see this counter has gone up almost 3%
Lupin appears normal up to 6:30%
Had accelerated and across also board farmer
You can also return your purchase to Space
If it is visible then sector reversal is one of its
If there is huge support then even if there is some small news
If it has come on a positive site then it could be
Translates into bigger games for counters
If it was seen happening then it makes sense because of this
Buy here for a target of 530
Pay Rs 5008 here on Stock Plus
If you want to move ahead then let's go on the basis of news.
Whatever stock we have, we have it with you.
Discussed but the last category is yet to be finalized.
There is still some left, I will bring my choice.
[music]
Sponsor New Platina 110 Abs Do You
Trading in the stock market
Isn't it every morning?
Now you will get ji busness and will show
India 360 Monday to Friday at 7:56 PM
at 5:00 PM on C Business
A wonderful and flawless journey
The number one market leader
The biggest name of trust but style
Absolutely common man whose experience and understanding
Even the giants salute in easy language only profits
That's why the country is running
[music]
Not every morning
by the storm of news
from the maelstrom of information
from the playful statements
by the web of rumours
Now you will get out
The app will also feature India 360 from Monday.
Friday evening at 7:56 p.m.
A wonderful and flawless journey
Leader
[music]
Moving on to the last and final category, Me Choice.
The stocks in the My Choice category from my side
I'll tell you what I've chosen.
First of all there is a bike tomorrow and that is
If you look at LT Mann, IT
I am constantly bihadish at the counters and G
The mood is currently favorable for TCS
And after the Infosys numbers, I was lost.
LT is still a sell-side candidate
remains in tomorrow's session although if you
If you look, there are two or three good counters.
You got to see a good rebound very quickly.
But ITM entry supports it.
If you are not able to see it at all then move ahead
It is possible that its numbers are relatively
worse than expected
If you can see it coming, it may be
Investors here, the big one is still on
If you are keeping yours then there is continuous weakness.
Let's do the one here on the chart and get to 4200
to the target and your stock will become plus
The second lot of 4370 is here on SBI
You are advised to buy it, in fact if you
If we look at the banks, the market has fallen.
Especially if you are a PSU bank here
Big support comes, that has been shown by the Bank of
Couples from Baroda had come
I told you about this counter and yesterday's
Even in the session, it remained in a bullish mood.
So overall the scenario has just been created
It has happened for the entire banking space
Market giant PSU bank's stance on SBI
Shopping still to do Ray Marie
Maintain target of ₹560 for today
And 535 will be your stop loss and who is the last one?
On IGL on IGL from my side
That's why the decision to buy is being made here
But because here Positive Broker is
The report appears to have come in and that is
On behalf of Morgan Stanley and IGL
The pricing here is around Rs 495.
Buy this and target 520
For this, stop loss has to be placed at Rs 485.
Mike, I have taken two stocks in this first.
That is Voltas and Blue Star, both of them
You will constantly see that mixed with the stars
News also came about the hit waves story.
Story in the states or story or no story
areas you are being given heat which is
If you look at it accordingly, then continuously
It is increasing and overall if you
If we look at it from these aspects, then both of them
For companies that use one color for both
If so, it may be that it is compatible here.
Whatever you like, business
Seen coming, will say bye to Voltas
The target will be 950 and the duration will be 6
Meena's similarly Blue Star's is also here
But I still want to buy and will keep the target at 1650.
And we will keep the duration of 6 minas and the third one and
The last stock I bought was GIC.
Because the star is the same G ICC Lombard
Keep flying in the way Kushal has given that
If the result appears to be quite large, then it is
If you look at the space, GIC
Compatibly, it could be that the result is
If you see better coming then GIC will help you here.
You will have to pay bye, we will keep the target of 150 rupees.
And we will keep the stop at 145, so the story
Na story scenario here for GIC
It also appears to be of good strength.
Overall, this results in Lombard's
If you see us coming, let's use the mike
All the stocks in the test category that you have
I have told you, but a quick recap is enough.
Let's do what our categories have been.
How to be the first to comment Som Distillery
Positive Update Company from Zee Way
That's quite a good update on the expansion here.
which has started commercial production with
JSW Smitha in He Metal Counters
Your accountant is already testing me positive.
Here is the ICC Lombard 1140 tomorrow option
You are advised to buy here as well.
Now fashion
Continuous week chart structure is
Let's do the big one here Mahindra and
Mahindra is looking good for the long term
Britannia remains the favourite among IPL stocks
ok throw it away
Go shopping for life science papers
Positive news appears to be here and Mike
In which category ITM entry bike
But SBI and its partner IGL
You get buying advice and all of these
Best Pick is Mahindra & Mahindra Next 1
Can you show me a target of 1400 rupees a year?
It is being said that in future he will become the TV lion.
You can see the market share game happening.
See how XUV400 bookings are open
We do it in cash, properties
The lines in futures are looking good.
This is a good news that the feature will help.
According to options According to options
If you look, you will see the picture of ONGC
There is an option, it has to be technically bought.
Mannapuram Finance is looking good
Fundamentally, there is enough space for ICC.
IPL is good as per stock
Prestige Street Project which is also
It looks pretty good according to the news.
Bachpan Enterprises Jahan Pe Seedha Bada Aai
There is a microphone which is available in Voltas and Blue Star.
Both, if you look at them, there are reports of them there.
But you can see the momentum coming and
Finally, if you talk about GIC, where
But the result of Log Mart is from there
It will be seen that there is benefit and in all this
My best pick would be Prestige
The straight project which is in G piece is
It is very good and the brand of the company too
If it is quite good then Prestige accordingly
Straight Projects
Now let's see when the saree will already be made.
The hair has been picked but it is still as it is
You said that even now you are there on Global
See here or in our market
See many sarees if you have clarity
So for all that clarity, let's go.
Deep Sir is already connected to Deepsar
Just in the mood for something a little cheaper
After a big boom, the global market also declined slightly.
Our markets have also become saturated with pulses.
Showing a consolidation trade from
Was there a hat-trick of consolidation today or
Taking you out of the range in the mid-week session
what are you doing
She keeps signs and tells you where she saw them.
Let's start Sher Bazaar Live
with headlines
[music]
Band 10 points below the level of sight 100 points above
The band slipped down to the mark
Dow futures down 60 points, flat near 700.
Hang Song 200's
The government has no intention of increasing capital gains tax.
The Income Tax Department has issued a scheme, not a plan.
Cleaning is also more on business news
Gold tumbles nearly $20 on weak dollar in 2015
Silver rose 1% to near $25.
Cruch oil below $85
The government has imposed a windfall tax on crude oil.
Increased from zero to 6400 per turn
Export duty on diesel reduced to zero
[music]
Thus Lombard took a 40% cut in profits.
Paid better than expected results today
Tata Communications' market performance
will be released
[music]
Bimal Land Assets to be listed today
The company was formed by the demerger of BML.
[music]
Cabinet meeting will be held today at 10:30 am.
meeting
Prime Minister Narendra Modi in Delhi today
Apple CEO to meet with
[music]
Ayurvedic with Research and Evidence
Medicinal Purpose Patanjali Dant Kanti Dadu's
Best Ayurvedic Toothpaste for
Patanjali Hair Kanti Advance Hair Fall
Prevent whitening in
[music]
Today it is cheaper than clouds all over the world.
Inside Nifty in both the signs and two
Performance and Bank Nifty out
After the performance, today is the day of Behad M
Tomorrow is the reality of futures trading.
Expiry so after the beginning what can we do
Will be able to hold the support level, there will be recovery
So how sustainable will it be today?
Trade delays, all questions and answers are preparation
Welcome to Sher Bazaar, hello everyone.
I am Anil Singh, hello, I am
Deepanshu Bhandari is looking at the mid-week market
action
Midweek is in 3 weeks.
If we say this, it can be said that it has been done for a week.
Now I understand where we haven't discussed it.
on the Europeans' habits of nanny
If you are in a good mood then tell me sir, what is your mood today?
It will be good, what are the bad signs?
See, the market will also get signals like us
Whatever she is doing, she is missing something.
They are not doing anything, so they
He is doing something and we are thinking that he is not doing anything.
So we don't have to do anything but this
If we look at it, it will hardly reach 200 again.
Their range has been banded 10 points lower
No, there have been four bands like this, just like
Yesterday the band went up by 2 points, due to which you
You can imagine what the atmosphere of Sasti is like.
Confirmation that capital gains tax will not increase
It has been done by the department and this is a big
Relief news that arrived yesterday at 1:00 p.m.
After the collection that triggered the sharp
The atmosphere was created and that news proved to be false.
has been
and ICC are of normal on d face
will analyze in detail and Tata
The results of communication are going to be declared today.
But I will keep an eye on it, I had a heavy tea yesterday.
Let's look at Tata Communications today.
How are Tata Communications on the outcome?
ICC Lombard reacts to the result
And at the rest of the insurance counters also you
Keeps an eye on the business going very flat
This is the big news on energy right now, which is tomorrow.
Let's talk to him first and start from there.
It started at 2:00 as we're talking
The thing was that half an hour ago he
The collection also came to the market at 1:30 pm.
In and its trigger was also believed to be
There were some reports that income tax
The news came from Badlapur, Capital Gen Tax
There may be a change in it but you said that
This is not possible, so once I
I want to hear what Anil ji said.
Then he also asks questions to Anil ji.
He scares us a lot at the mention of our habit.
We have become accustomed to the name STD
I am very scared that this STD had increased, right?
After the budget, I forgot that day and everything.
It is not useless if those who know this news
Will the gold market go bad on the spur of the moment?
It will be accepted, that is a useless thing, finance
This news is coming from ministry sources.
Changes in the rules of capital gains tax
There are no plans from their side. Source
There is news of Base and our Finance Ministry
Sources tell us that such
There are reports of changes in tax rules.
He is wrong, there is no such idea that
Finance Ministry changes tax rules
Do this and this is the long term news of Bihar.
The news of increase in capital gains tax
A is being made to recover the tax refund
Finance Ministry should consider this with a panel
Create a committee and maybe I'll reduce it.
But our sources are telling us this
that the Finance Ministry will take no such action
not going to take
So analysis is done in the time before the news comes.
The market reacted and you were right.
That you said that this is the logic behind it.
If you apply it's not going to happen and then
Later we looked at the accounts of our sources
It came from me that this is going to be new and then
After that the IT department
Clarification official classification also on this
Gave the reading, not the situation
When the market starts falling sharply after
I used to think that we said why did it fall when
I saw that this report came on Blubber that maybe
Long term capital and tax should be increased
Such news may be coming like this
The proposal is going on with the Finance Minister.
After that we emptied our logical gear
He has thought about it, we have no news at the moment.
It wasn't supposed to happen, it wasn't supposed to happen
What was the logic, the budget has just ended.
Hey, if you had to talk about the budget then after the budget
STDs are big, so why not this?
Executively correct and the third and most
The important thing is that when in equity
Worldwide taxes at normal rates
they seem less so because he
consider investment and that risk
If you need capital for the country then we
why would we do this separately and the fourth thing that
The most important thing is your tax collection
It is so strong, it is so strong tax
If the collection is like this then it means tax
The deficiency is in the government's expectations
What is excess tax collection?
Accessories Why You Create A Nice Special Atmosphere
In which a few thousand crores more tax has to be collected.
Market mood for the entire April
Where the capital racing hard
If it happens then this was a logical thing, this was our
2:10 was the analysis and then we thought that
Why should we find out how much truth is there in the news?
How much have we got from our friend's ministry?
When we found out from the sources, then after that
Did you also get good news like this?
We told you there will be no changes, thank you.
God thank you Income Tax Department by the way
Income Tax Department
[music]
so that the confusion is removed, whether we say
Someone else may say something but if the ministry says or
Then if the Income Tax Department says so, then his income
People will believe more in accuracy than we do.
The source is telling but what is in the source
We told the Income Tax Department from there.
said that there was no such proposal yesterday.
This tweet has already come before you, so brothers
Calm down on the meaningless things
Don't panic if the matter escalates.
If a small market is to fall
Should such news come, they would fall down
Adversely, I don't think anyone is big on this.
The issue is
At least till the next budget, we can rest easy.
I am asleep, we will see at the time of the next budget.
To come or not to come
I don't think that at this time anyone is doing something like this.
You will need your thing
And if this spoils someone's mood
Look, the market has to fall and it has to increase.
It is a different thing but the reason should be right, right?
So because of this, on one side the incident bill
You will get a big positive for today here too.
Mother can do that if people who
It was the stone that saw this news and
Reduced or shorted the position accordingly
If you look at it, this is good news.
Clarification has been given and immediate clarification has been given.
Right from the mouth of the forces, so from this
Well, what you need is a little of that.
Understanding the situation, you must panic.
No, I reached the station at 2:00 pm yesterday.
If it is perfect then clarification is given in this
on the issue and you should be concerned
It is not there and you also find peacock in our news.
It has been seen, well this was good action.
Sir, let's talk about our market too.
First, let's look at the consolidation that has happened.
I would also like to ask you about this in the US markets.
I wish you had said something about our millets.
I haven't reacted to the opener, but yes one.
Check with the doctor how he is doing.
Results of four-five banks in America today
There is no reaction at all yesterday.
Both Goldman Sachs and Bank of America
This is the result but we did not react to it.
See, it means you are not in the mood to do anything.
The whole day in four to five points
Trade is happening sir what is this reaction
Not giving is also a reaction
I've decided what it looks like.
I will not react, this is my reaction.
My reaction
But the thing is, who are these DPs, you and I?
What should the market of the decider depend on?
How much, when and why should one react?
The beauty of the market is that sometimes the thing that
Big reaction to this not being important
A goes by and you think, oh man, this
what was there in it, why so much and so many times
It is an important thing but it does not come
Actually, you have a perspective on this.
What is the American perspective?
If we also have a boom on one side and
Playing American after her fast time here
We are here to follow the American truths
We
America – We started after 5 days of knowing
This time we will delay a little bit.
were running so the US markets ran away first
First the nearest part then both the consulates
Correct, this is what has happened in America in the last three
Take out the data for the week and see it.
What happened here, we are running a little late.
Start and last two after running late
We are also showing the same thing from both, so where
As far as the global market is concerned, nothing
Has there been any major change in your closed deals?
There is a change, there is a big change in the dollar index
Crude oil prices are getting higher
Floods are passing and gold and silver are running high
Gold dollar 25 in both up and down range
Nothing new is happening, nothing new is happening
If there is only one result of these companies
Here is the market's reaction to those results.
Now what is the problem in this, it is also strange
The results are coming, do you have any reaction on this?
When is the reaction visible in the overall index?
Now a little bit about Netflix's fallout today.
There will be a reaction which is due to the market being band
If the marks are a little bad then this is the reason
You may find the Dr Recipe features a bit subdued.
I am looking a little down today
Net has been fixed for the market to be band
After that I have to understand that unless someone special
Until a new treasure is created, it will remain like this.
Triggers that are being tried to be created are now quite
The people of America came in hushed tones.
Mean people mean my bank economist
There are people in the market, they should say that bass
Rates will be increased not once but twice, this is a new
Some countries may also become trigger points tomorrow.
Free country also became like that because of which such
It seems that if a new two times now here
I have given you an important thing because now it is there.
When we know that the market is slow then
Now market reaction on what next thing
Now it is important to guess what he will do.
One thing you can do is put it inside.
Whatever is possible your mind can do
that this can happen and the other thing is if something
If you go out of syllabus, you will be out of syllabus.
If you don't know then you have to think about it.
What new thing can America give and that is
Two Fed members gave two more
Hearing about the increase, I fired the bullet not once but twice.
Sir also said that he gave the range
the big one
started taking it seriously
Then tomorrow you will get one or two of them.
By the way, American Dove futures are down at 10 tomorrow.
Bands Hue Lekin De Hyper Bands Hue
Both bands were around, moving in different directions.
So I think the next big trigger is next
If the market is to be moved for both one and two
If the Americans start thinking about it,
If you give the lamp or not, the bass will increase twice.
The market is ready to go down a little from here.
ok yes
Afternoon is not ready, I mean, twice anyway.
The US market for Mentally is still
Not prepared, at most one
If you hike that last honey twice
If there are chances of a hike then clouds will appear.
It will be difficult to stay up
What kind of rates are there in the US?
The atmosphere is created in the next two-three days.
Keep this in mind until Friday.
First point, second point, no result, very
It is good, it is very bad, if he loses his temper
I don't know because from the results here
If you don't know then what can I say about there
If you have any reaction then please give these two
I'll keep an eye on the transistors.
It happened there for our millets too, sir.
One interesting thing and I want to highlight
I would like to talk to you about this again
Yesterday we thought it was good at the index level.
Almost flat action with great range
There was business but stock specific moves you
It has come well, especially midcap and small
Let's take a look at the capsule first.
What did people have to say yesterday, then for today
How will the money be made
If the stock spreads, the stock which you
Delivery
Position trophy for and whom you mood
Wanted to buy after the atmosphere became good
They
GO IT
And we had the same thing happen yesterday as well.
There is also some market consolidation from both.
Gaya But N Bitcap Index Dekho Sir Days
Hyper Bands Pound Rising by 10%
Good action in small caps as well
There is a lot of AMO in the broad market.
What you said is even more so now.
Expect some index for both
need more stock than should have to
Your Nifty may move up by a thousand points.
from Strone and went nonstop and after
Slight outperformance of stocks is also a
Now you are in cash market stocks
Isn't that the bullish thought of 2022 in April?
So we don't get it that way
Quality and quality will not be in stock everywhere
There will not be any but still the broad market
Looks like it's getting a little better for you
This is clearly visible, so I thought right now today
Also Deep and next week at least for friendship
Even the children of April are less likely to give you a month's worth of food.
Quality Mid Curse Going to Quality
The action is fixed and on the same condition
have to buy
Yes, the company is likely to get good results.
Confidence or even a little bit, good results
I don't know if they will come or if they will come bad or where
Reals will be bad, next quarter will be good
These ones will come, they will be bad, don't buy them.
He doesn't take well again
You thought, okay, this is bad, isn't it?
The difference is the result of the next quarter, so there
There will be improvement from there, someone will be better from there
It doesn't matter, it doesn't matter
The scooter is expected to arrive defective or you
I don't know whether it will be good or bad
Anything he avoids now will be because of the consequences.
Take the example of confidence later.
Government Banks will give you results with confidence
good good will come
Two out of 25 public sector banks and five public sector banks
If the bank gives me 20 rupees, I won't give you that much now.
So you will have to think who these 20 are.
Whatever good you can give
You have to choose, like that space
You know the results are good there.
Fox any company like this
Specific risk of loss to you
Not there.
If you want to carry it on stock then it is good
Focus on companies that deliver results
Because look, the market has to do something.
will have to do when indexing was giving chance
If you get a chance to have a big capsule in the index
They are not big but they will all work for you.
One has to be selective and understand
It has become ingrained in my mind that I have to do this.
Then you have to select the stock.
Your positioning is just stock again.
Selection becomes less easy
and then see
It is safe
Meaning
The market is there to make your money.
It's too much, I understand, okay, yesterday you did something
Excellent
Three-four investment mantras were given in which
You said this stock would have been mental even today
I told you two-three things, Done Global
in the market and a little in our market
a little time to spend after a quick trip to one side
The process is time wise consolation.
That will happen and should happen and the health of the market
Cash market showrooms are also suitable for
The action will increase a little more slowly.
It will grow selectively but will grow well.
How to mark the quality at this time
We will give you full opportunity to make money and two things
And is above 175 as long as Nifty band is being
Till then you should trade for short term.
But there is no need to worry if it is below 17,500.
If you have a band then you will have to do your training.
One should reduce the position and close below 41000
Sorry if Bank Nifty below 41500
If there is a band, you should reduce the position.
As long as these two are above closing
On the basis of bio dips till then ji day their
Downstairs bands will be her day short term
Reduce or close trading positions
Then we will wait again, it is clear to you
Yesterday was definitely bad but X
If we look at Reliance, Nifty has more
Difficulty
Your Reliance has been downgraded, you think about it.
The day before yesterday it was open 3% higher
I mean from there, yes
Otherwise, Nifty was not in such a great condition.
of which and the bank too is completely on your side.
I will try to support you exactly two
IT wasn't that bad yesterday either
In fact, it is active in the second half.
Bad results, not overall sector performance
Dal Paega and any IT communication
If a good performance is given then the lion will be good.
I think it can also run a race.
Now in the company, the party of soil is weak
Results are very good, very good in action
I can, the only problem is that I don't
I wanted it to flood before the results.
But from tomorrow onwards, before the results, I will start studying.
Gave the signal and today from Gardner's side too
A guidance has come regarding teachers
He has maintained his, so has my
I think that is also a positive story.
If they did not see the problem then this
This is a big deal for a global IT company.
From today onwards that is a good and important thing so
IT support should have been a little better
5 years ago back
had hit
There was a direct link with the currency of the rupee.
Purpose: When and which lamp will be available in the market?
The trigger will reduce the risk for a sector.
It is necessary to get hold of me, there was a time when
Remember inflation figures used to come at 12:00 pm?
Sir used to come every week at 2:00 pm, yes
And on the basis of expensive figures, Sensex fell
So that means one percent and two percent.
keep coming and changing the triggers and this IT
For companies, the trigger is gone.
The weakness or strength of the rupee is because
and a period of time of many years in it
The company understood that our dollar came
in front of us
Correct, so keep these dollars with you.
Finance in IT company if you get it
This is the biggest achievement of the department.
Hedging and Treasury Management
So there is nothing left, just salary has to be paid.
Small expenses like computer lights etc.
Everything else inside the bill is theirs and something else.
If not, we have to reduce the dollars we are getting.
Keep them properly, they may go up and down
So you want predictable honey sir and second
This is the extra money that is lying in cash.
Unless you're distributing the lion holder.
It doesn't seem to be there in the expansion.
Management just needs to know where to invest it.
Such defloration
I was in a bit of a frenzy yesterday, recovering.
Today there is some news about ITO also.
I will highlight for you today in a little fear
Let us understand the strategy first sir
Global crisis slightly on the negative side
Keep the lamp I have changed from negative to neutral mother
Fees can also be indicated negatively.
Can be on the neutral side
Neutral mother can indicate pheno
Sentiment is neutral, train is positive
It is neutral, okay, today only one support John
I have given NIFT
17517575 This is strong support, this is the only thing that matters.
everything else is useless okay okay
We may try to take support from 17625
Do what we were doing yesterday 625
17575 support which is there for today from here
Starts right up to 17750 ago
If you pass through the obstruction then it will cost 800-850
That Ranji where you get 100% profit booking
should do
Support for you John below it 41 525 41
525 is 100% by John, however low it will go.
No, if you accidentally find this range nowadays
Must buy in
just like 175 okay up 42 542 600
Parker's is a place for light interruptions.
If it comes out then that range is 42825 to 42950 or
Both profit booking and bike wali to you
You must do this, it is very good for you sir
In two days we have seen consolidation
Its position was a little less than its height.
The quality show has become quite comfortable.
Look, it has reduced compared to yesterday's two
Nifty which has decreased and yesterday Bank TV
If it was a flat then the fees would be as per that.
There is no change in the index position.
Nifty decreased slightly, banks lost a little.
It is comfortable, is there any special change in it
17500 for existing long positions
Our 25 point comfort john lekker 17475
You can take 17,475 to its level.
and Bank Nifty
42000 You can also interchange if you want
Intraday to anyone as per your convenience
I have kept Rs 42000, I can keep anyone.
If you want to keep closing stop at 41800 then
There are both levels, do whatever you like.
Okay, short side short side 17850
Entertainer on closing basis both your
This is the Stackclose and on Bank Nifty
Hi you made 42600 the day before yesterday 42
It was worth 500, a little above 42 mustard seeds.
You can take the interior closet of Rs 42,625.
can
Gotted sir ok new position 17525 17600 this
That's the range you should shop in.
If Nifty reaches this range a little
Good times 500 500 525 550 around 500
around a little and collect in pieces
You can do it in two or three pieces.
shopping
Find a suitable stock of 17475 or 17450
The target that will be made is 17650
750 is the medium target and 17,800,825 is the final target.
You have to click on the target and make a purchase.
I
100% sending in the range of 17750 to 17825
Do we want to sell it at 17800 or 17700 only?
I will decide it in time, not doing it now.
The current decision is between 750 and 825.
Why am I talking about selling 17700?
When you ask me for Fino data then
If I tell you, ₹17750 ₹725 is the perfect range.
Sell ​​the stock at 17900 plus the target
Which will become 17700 and 17650 which are smaller targets
625 and 600 are two medium targets and 17575
It is okay to do it for the target
inch shopping
The target is to be set at ₹750 which will be made
42175 Two small targets
7542 375 Two Medium Targets till 4227
Buy opinion from stock of Rs 42000 for
I gave it today and I am still studying from yesterday.
Keep it in the same range and that too from today also.
Okay, buy stoppers worth 42000 from him.
₹375 ₹450 are two small targets 500 and 600
The medium target is 42725 and the big target is 42725.
For which you have to do it, you have to buy it, okay
Sir Dan
I
You can create a mood even with 450 but with 500
600 This range appears to be obstructing
The top of both is here, here first
Start at 725 and then you can go up
Are
The target will be 42850 which will become 42 450 more
42 375 Two small targets
42275 42150 Two Medium Targets 42000 41800
To be done for the final target of up to
9 days straight positive band has been done
only one day out of 12 days
11 out of 12
I am telling you therefore
100 million 1 crore 27 lakh
There you can band it down a little bit.
We are leaving today, listen carefully, till then you can fast
I am not
17725 By completing the first condition
Create a bullish mood only if you survive, other vices
You delay it, this is an important thing.
There is a big change
The condition for you is Tagdi Gold Rate
Is
and then the highest open at 17,500
Interest Foot in So Broadley Range which appears
I am on top 70725 is on the bottom
17575 17 shows are currently showing
Bank 42000 strong support 32 lakh shares there
But in open interest and balls 500 yesterday
Letters are standing here 42 lakh lion miles away.
There will be definite profit booking around 5600
because
If not, book profit and get Rs 42000
Only after going below you will be able to get into the market.
If he thinks then it seems like both the banks
Someone from the side is ready to do a special story.
I don't have any time, I will spend some more time
And but there is a slight uptrend in Nifty
Oxide Limited is visible, hence tomorrow
You'll remember that tomorrow we'll talk about this too.
If Nifty is not the loan lender then the bank
is being seen
That it will take sweat to do it, the results
need something good
Absolutely nothing in futures 70 codes
Index of and Stock Features worth ₹187 crore
Was the quality of Rs 800 crore even special?
400 crores is not a big deal to read local in front of
Cricket is fine in
Real also forgot what it had to do, ICC fox
Number face off fit if you look at year 10
You should be very strong this year
Your net interest net premium
Your profits are 12% higher and 40% higher this year.
10 years number six but you don't get a quarter
Those who are not strong enough to have good grandchildren
One reason for this is net premium income
This is what they have earned and others are theirs.
Commission expenses have reduced slightly.
The results from that look strong, I think.
of the Indian Ex which belongs to the temple
But if I look at the quarter earth, I will see a little
The market share of other rations has also decreased.
So if you look at it, the numbers are that strong.
No, that's probably why there are no major upgrades.
So there is no one but those who are like doctors
They have reduced their targets slightly.
Now, but there are a couple of things that go along with it.
It is important and it is done throughout the year.
The Lions haven't done anything in a year.
From now till now, the lion is 13%
That means bad results, the price is also quite high.
I have to go now, the bad result is price in it.
But it increased by 4% in the last week, now it
This result is 4% bigger than last week
Because of this the market was big or was it bullish? Correct
It is difficult to say if it is like hockey
4% purchases were made, this would not have happened until then
I used to say that if I commit a crime below, then surely
Shot but still in stock 52
been running around under the weeks so I
Think it's not too much of a fall, honey.
Should come if profit booking increases
will go
If it sits open, the covering will come from below
It seems so but still I will return once again today.
Let's watch, I am very focused on the price area
Confident does not want to give clear opinion
See how the market is late, I understand.
Sir it's okay
The result is that you will get a reaction.
This is a bit of a result with our team as well.
Latest news and details about Brockley's
I talk to Armaan and Nupur as well
Ashish is ready with us, tell us your wishes
What are the triggers and clothes doing today?
There are definitely results and many sarees
There are also triggers in which if you
Let me tell you about Tata Communications
The post market may result in
ICC security seen coming in cash
And Alok Industries is where you will see
BML Land Assets, which is seen getting results,
From today their list will be visible.
Global Surface will be visible Shipping Corporation of
India, here's where you need to be careful.
Because now he will be included in a group
from the TV group because if you
If you look at the price band,
Management now increasing from 5% to 20%
It will be seen that there is a cabinet meeting, right?
as well as the UK's global
CBI and P data for the month of March
March will be seen in Europe
CBI data will come and if you look at the result
Talking about Tata Coffee, here if you
If we look at the overall result, it will come to about 10%.
It is good that you have increased by a margin.
You will see that here the cut is 17%.
Seen falling to 15% and profits
However, if you look at 20% profit
increasing authority over the results that
This was the banner of the director I met.
Show that he said instant
The coffee business has been performing exceptionally well.
Apart from that, if you look at the demand from Africa
Whatever is lacking in me remains
Okay, so here are your results, Tata Coffee, on this.
reaction is also reaction
64% on domestic crude production
Winkfool tax has been imposed and the price on diesel
Export duty has been completely removed.
Diya, it is not torture but dare since 19th
If implemented, all these stocks
You will also be in focus on IT stocks
Keeps an eye on it because it has a chance of biting
The conference is tomorrow where they
Current 2023 global IT spending and
Growth guidance has been maintained.
The last increase they made was 5.5%.
He's retained you right stock Fox
I live in the state where the company's
Subsidiary has made an acquisition 51%
Dhan Sun has bought the stake for Rs 66 crore.
or tag decoration technology
If this stock shows positive results then this stock
is going to be in for Piramal Pharma as well
Let there be some positivity, see here
Pay USA FDNA company which that
There is a facility, it has been given air, so here
The pay inspections that were in place are over.
So this will be in stock today Fox Vespa
Enterprises where again the quarter four
Share in the last half percent
Earlier it was ₹250, now it has been increased to 3%
And lastly, Evalo Technology which listed yesterday
It happened there that bulb deals were seen taking place.
Goldman Sachs has invested around Rs 3.5 lakh
Buy shares at the price of Rs 412
Goldman Sachs not listed here
I will still be in Fox to buy shares today.
Let's go to Ashish, don't you know what's going on today?
Saree Brokerage Reports Again
[music]
Good Morning Deepanshu watch first
ICC Lombard General Insurance here
The company's results came after reports
The UBS report is significant because
Shopping Cara has been retained
Closing is 1131, target given is 1445
But pay special attention to the country this Monday.
Their profits are better than expected
It has been seen here but climes
Growth is still largely elevated
The premium has been lower than the industry
and combined fibers are still elevated
Also, if you look at the guidance that
Similar to what was seen here
Shopping Kara has maintained its target of Rs 1500
Mughal style has reduced to 1400 overweight
The rating of the Galaxy A1400 is filled with
And he is also saying that whatever they
The profits have been better than their estimates.
Growth seen here GP Morgan
has maintained its neutral rating
Target cut from 1250 to 1160
Have a buy opinion on this
He has also scored 1620 runs on the target.
to 1560 and most
well below the current market price
The target is given for Rs 995, apart from this Titan
Good report from the sewing team here.
Shopping Cara has retained its target
Increased from ₹3000 to ₹3150
Closing is 2578 and IGL is here too
If you see, this is a good report, Maugans Rally.
Where the overweight rating has been given by
Lakshmi has also been increased
The stock price has increased from Rs 5007 to Rs 540.
It is around ₹500 and the mother is
Good growth can be seen here
is 16 1/2% of this gear by volume
He is moving ahead with this expectation and whatever
Changes were also made in the gas policy.
OK, so Don and Top Reports will be beneficial.
Yes, but something else
Deepanshu Zomato here from UBS
Reporter Shopping Kara is retained
The target has been reduced from 90 to 80, but now
Also see according to current market price
So there's quite a lot of websites because 53 of
Closing is going on tomorrow India continuously
Report wants GP Morgan still
Prices are expected to rise again
Orbit's rating has been retained and
The goal is to increase it slightly first.
The target was ₹285, now a little more
Now the police have to give a target of ₹290.
However the stock is trading at 232 on LNT
Here is a report from Bamboo.
The target was increased from 200247 to 20042
The news that came yesterday about United Spirits
Note wicket after this towards inquiry
The report has come from inside performance rating
775 closing at 650
There is a coin view and finally just dial tomorrow
Where we also saw the impact of the result
Reported by the City
maintains a buy opinion and
Top line up around 14% till Monday's f5 25
You can see the growth of power here.
Due to which their goal is
₹666 has been increased from ₹735 to ₹815
closing is
If everyone's targets do not change then generally target
does not change
Target in Titan
In Zomato which starts from ₹5 in India but
The target is there, the target is made in L&T
Backed by a strong panel of experts
All our time is
[music]
Good morning to all of you
What happens after you get home from school?
A child spends the day playing and doing his homework
The rest is relief and then she's at school in the morning.
He comes to class, his teacher comes.
I will complete it quickly first.
[Laughter]
The stock that is on my radar right now is
MFL MFL these stocks inside mere ko g
It is expected that the mouth will be formed from here tomorrow.
In stock tomorrow in stock show good face
And KGF also continues in this stock.
Those who have created positions should take it
Those people may hall do any shopping
If you want, then here and from here if someone
A lamp also comes for seven-eight rupees, going up to ₹640-42
So buy on load levels I decide
inside
Support or stock plus will form below 632
So stock of 632 for long positions
Apply and invest in Max Financial above
The target could be 670's first digital
If the second target of 680 is made then from one
Shop for Two Both Max
Financial 632 Stop plus 670 more
For targets of 680
Okay, so this is your Max Financial.
Opinion on buying in Bansal ji, good morning
Tell me sir, your Prashant's lion
Good morning
Kunal ji and I also informed Shukla while leaving.
had given
There has been a good deal of speculation and this stock
Can also become a dark horse meaning
Stop loss is to be placed at 293.313
Target
A small way to increase your knowledge a little more
I want, as you just said, that Sumit
Yes, when some children go home from class, they do homework.
If you are not able to do it then quickly do AK in the morning
are doing
So there are some children who are not taken
No force outside the examination hall
Meaning that they keep moving around, keep moving around and
Harassing nearby batchmates
Such a mean, studious boy like Sami ji
what have you read
I will study, spoil theirs.
He might know it but to check
Many such children rely on the confidence of others.
GI who gives confidence to others
Kunal ji, who raised the issue, is also with us.
Kunal ji, good morning, tell me sir, your pick up
Dee Dee
Good morning
Deepanshu Anil ji has a buy opinion and
As Bansal ji said that pharma stock
I am seeing you again Anandi and another
Breakout also coming on the Pharma Index
If you can see it, then my opinion is also to buy it.
There is stock on the pharma company and that pharma
In which we have seen tremendous growth
Well, I think a major breakup.
It has come on the chart and you can buy this stock at 620 630
If you want to have the power to show the levels of
Say bye to these stars and move on to 566
Keep stop loss at 66, these two are 590 and 610
targets for which in and off pharma
Shop 590 610 Aurobindo Pharma Forgot
Forgotten stocks seen getting into action
Buying opinions were divided here and this
From here we did it continuously from 450 to 460.
I don't want to go to the temple very slowly.
It would be better but it would run so fast
Good morning, welcome, tell me sir.
Your pick of Dee Dee
aa good morning energy kabhi dar se search kar
I was one of those students who
It always takes place outside the examination hall.
Is
If I don't study at home then last 10 minutes
After much heroic fighting, I became a
I have got the stock, the name of the stock is Mfish, think
You were studying outside an empty examination hall.
Thinking you reached here with so little education
Like Bansal ji, he keeps on calling for hours.
So you arrive
[music]
I saw with great force that all around me
People are very big
When I started, I actually felt like this
If you read the early part of your career
If yes, then like me, I will read it to you later.
If you don't need to, honestly speaking
I'm a very bad student and I'm a gym student
What you are doing right now is amazing.
Are not ultimately fast important
The present is important for that you
Please also say good luck sir
Oh thank you Anil ji Anil ji see I
Quite good stock and Kunal ji and I
I completely agree with Rakesh ji.
In fact, I should also give only farmer stock.
Wanted but not you get an panel crowd
So I took some resistance and
The stock selection I have made is from the IT space.
And that is Emphasis and I probably hear you
I was saying that you are talking about IT stocks.
The same CX IT has become quite lucrative
I have a major breakdown but from
Trading Perspective Parley Trading
The perspective is that of Impress Empresses
The clue is yesterday's 783 means 1783 and a very
This beautiful double bottom hammer has made me
It seems only on the basis of
Technicals take a good contrast here
Can keep a stoppage of 1740 and like
The same stock was taken out above 1830 which was my first
Target: I think the stock will go up to 2000
So I have to buy it from MP with intraday stop.
Loss 1740 Target 1830 and ok so this is it
Buy Mfaces Exclusively For You
Opinion: Only these two spaces appear strong.
If you like the variety and speciality of pharma
It seems that the two forms he gave
So if you become prudent then it is exactly like this
You understood it, because Kunal ji, Rakhi ji
Early morning pic of de de different
Absolutely, but the ITB is strong.
This world will not only doubt but also emphasize
Opinion from Ji came for you Amritsar too
Amritsar Good Morning Welcome with us
Please tell me yours too sir please give me pickup
Narayana Hrudayalaya from the health care segment
It has around 47 health care facilities.
There are about 22 hospitals, including 21 primary hospitals.
There are health care facilities and Kar Health
They have centers of about 600 beads.
It has a capacity of 67 operations.
You are a doctor according to their rules.
About 1.5 hai which is extremely good
Sitting at Rs 40 lakh, it is the lowest in this category.
I got good marks but 9 months fee is due on 23 December
Of
Revenue around 20% you were awarded ₹300 with
Improve Contribution from New Hospital
N Mumbai Hospital where the new
Hospital was its rich de break and level
Two new NCR companies are positive contributors
Command from hospital to Ireland's hospital too
Showing good growth which was de
The problem is early off to overall EBITDA which is
The last three currently account for about 21% of these.
In quarters, he spent
About 680 crores in the last quarter
Which is expected to expand in January-March?
you about 32
will be spent on f5 23 and f5 24
We are saying that fear of spending and
Thousand crores and cap picks so its jo
Growth visibility is quite good.
Expected DC on f5 25 is around 32
And my target here is 960
OK 960 Here you can buy by setting a target
Make this counter of Narayan Vidyalaya also yours
You should be afraid of the stock that came today.
Will counter react once on him too
The cheque should be taken once ICC Lombard
Look at the charts, let's talk quickly.
What were the important levels?
Technical for this
Deepanshu, I have been listening to the discussion for a long time.
and I felt like the stock was very
Could do well because the stock hasn't moved
It is 1440 in 2019 and 2021
I walked a little bit, went up to 1600, after that
The stock has not gone lower in the last 2 years.
And off the range is beautiful around thousand
I think these are easy stocks in the mouth
It could go up to 1280, which is a conservative assessment.
should happen and now fundamentally in the way
There's news flow, I think stocks and
If you want to do well then technical education
Expect target up to 1240 and go down
OK, then you can target up to 1200.
ICC Lombard see tomorrow so off course
Towards and off trading great speak came
I was and I saw this band on the day when
You will see such a tall man in action today.
Tata Coffee also got its results yesterday and
The results we got were few and the results we got were not special.
As much as perhaps the coffee price which jumps on a
I had an expectation, Sumit ji, say goodbye once.
Sir, please see the coffee chart.
Move the stock by holding the position within
Rebound from lower levels after an internal decline
And after seeing Raven, this
consolidating a bit but
The stock should move upwards from here.
Inside, there is a support at the bottom above the charging
is around 200 and above
Resistance is around ₹215, you are 14 you
15 Once this level is broken upwards, it will reach 220
Upward move in Tata Coffee from Rs. 225 to Rs.
If it is formed on the other side, then those who have created positions
Shop up to ₹220 off at Halal Deep
Tata Coffee to look for an upside move
Ko Milan Chahiye OK Amritsar Track
Tata Coffee no opinion after result coffee
We have also seen prices increase recently.
In fact, if you look at it today, it is 6 months old.
Coffee prices are at their peak, sir.
A lot of money is flowing in, I think debt bills
Good but Tata Coffee so I think here
Pay if collection comes
This will create a good buying opportunity.
ICC Lombard Sir, do you also have any views?
On the numbers
Medium to long term pay here
Insurance sector is the only one to pay
negative that
I have just received news that insurance
The controversy surrounding the booking expense
It's happening, I don't know which one
Insurance company is involved, bats from them
If he is involved then there is no clarity on this.
This is only negative which is Devar D
If not the insurance sector, then this bin inside
Perform in the last 18 months high time
date it perform so i mean if you are
Talking of D
ICC in the overall insurance sector
Lombard made quite an impression
So Amritsar's positive on ICC Lombard
Let's see how it looks after the result today.
Reaction comes on this counter also
integration of what Indian exports had done
After that I am definitely getting the benefit
Reliance Industries will also keep an eye on this
Firstly, the windfall tax has been withdrawn.
There is a fault of Rs 6400 per 10 on crude.
X has been put on but diesel
Zero tax on exports has been completely removed.
For now, Singapore Village also
Your 6 month old baby is due tomorrow.
There was some pressure on the stock, Kunal ji
Sir, please see the chart of Reliance, yesterday's fall
After this, now the important levels for today
What will become of it
Deepanshu is the most critical level on the chart
It is a star of magnitude 2310 and around 340
If it is band then I think it will cost 20-30 rupees
Below you will see a large support.
2310 level if Reliance holds
I think it's quite likely
And there are no new cell positions in these
Effects should be made around 2300 whose
I have an existing shot in my driveway
They should book profits
Okay, so this is Reliance for you like Kar
I am weak, let's move forward and give you a
Big and experience exclusive news
Let's take it towards diversion.
Our correspondent Tarun from New Delhi joins in
Sharma is with us in the program right now.
have been included and Tarun has one each
First on the front of three updates
IDBI Bank Tell us immediately IDBI Bank
How fast has KV investment picked up pace?
How far has the car reached? What are the updates?
The dish investment of the bank is its own
It is in the final stages and the company notification
RBI has been
Many big names are processing
This includes those who have invested in IDBI Bank.
If you have applied for disinvestment
It is expected that we will do it by three
IDBI Bank's monthly dish
The investment must be completed
Because the names have been
So after this the special bits are open
It will happen and the hope is that in the next 3 to 4
This process was completed within a month.
will go and because this year the government wants
The government has already set a very low target.
The target is 50 thousand crores
about disinvestment
In which IDBI is a major bank
Whose investment is to be made, the process is final.
The air started because
Disinvestment is a big blow
If you have to park them at the stop
Because of this, it is now expected that from the next three
Tax is of IDBI Bank in the month which
There is disinvestment, it will be completed, okay.
IDBI Bank's net profit in three to five months
Expected to complete the registration and some
Big and interesting names are coming forward.
Who can bid for it?
Update regarding ID Pay Bank at this time
Apart from this, Shipping Corporation is the second
Diversification candidate is here too Puri
The market is watching, tell me what kind of things are there
You have updates
Yes, I would like to mention that shipping
Corporation of India's demerger already
You have been approved, you are at the first stage.
His listing is honey listing hope
They are doing this either by the end of this month
By or within the first week of listing
The listing of non-car assets by Bhim
It will be completed, Bhim
After completing Financial Bits Open
If this is done, it is expected that
Shipping Corporation till the last week of I
of India which are financial bits
They will be opened and
This can be expected by the end of this year
that of the Shipping Corporation of India also
Diversification should happen completely but
The thing about listing non-car assets
that he was in the last week of March or I
I hope to do this in the first week.
Sources are confirming that
Listing of more assets soon
Ho Shakti is there and after this listing of Bhim
Only financial bits will be opened
Okay, so this is also a big deal for you.
The update is that listing is underway soon.
At this time Shipping Corporation is clear
No bids till the end of Interesting Me
Hey, that means how many children do you have?
Dead Month Dead Month Dead Month
I'm looking at the end of the mic for you
And the third request is to NMDC.
Tarun, tell me what kind of people are there?
There are updates
For the steel plant of NMDC
There is quite aggressive bidding power and
It is hoped that this
There are financial bits, open them quickly.
And many big companies are interested in it.
In his expression of interest, he
The country's big steel has shown interest
The company has shown interest in this.
All steel companies except Tata Steel and
All steel companies except POSCO
If you have shown interest in this then just hope
It is being said that soon its financial
bits should be opened and because this
The biggest asset of the year will be
will go into digestion, the process of which
Still running and at a good valuation
Here and NMDC Steel is expected to meet
I hope so because of this
Financial bits should also be opened soon.
There is hope but these are the sources
What is known from this side is that in this
The interest is in very large steel
The company is interested and because right now it
The plant was to be operational from March 31, which
It has happened partially but right now this is the complete process.
The operation has not been done yet as soon as the operation
Its valuation will increase further
and then the financial bits of it
should be opened
So here comes a big lesson for you.
They are visible and as always, this time too
Our team is fully prepared
All news related to diversification is the best
First, to get to know you, Tarun told you
How IDBI Bank Shipping
Corporation and NMDC Steel
Talks regarding diversification moved forward
Thank you for showing up and immediately coming to all these lions
Our experts will also take some fear
But before that, let's start with the headlines.
First trade with
[music]
Limited availability of election also resulted in flat bands
American market servants only friends we reform
Band near heights of 10
Points down then Jas from above then points slipped
The band retreated by 4 points
Futures hang down 50 points near HA 700
Song drops by 100 points
[music]
There is no provision for the government to increase capital and taxes.
The Income Tax Department has issued a scheme, not a plan.
Death on the news of Safai Ji Business
[music]
In the final stages with a great response
Access IDBI Bank Disinvestment Shipping
I will be called to the end for the corporation
Bids were also received for the NMDC steel plant.
Wedding is also possible in a month.
Business news
[music]
Government reduces winfall tax on crude oil to zero
increased to ₹6400 per turn on diesel
Export duty reduced to zero
ICC Lombard defrauded 40% of profits
With the same results as expected by Pace
Tata shirts in futures trading today
Communications results will come
[music]
Bhim Land Assets to be listed today
The company was formed from The Merger of BML
[music]
Dant Kanti is best for teeth
Ayurvedic Toothpaste and Patanjali Kesh Kanti
Advance New Hair Growth in Hair Fall
Prevent whitening
[music]
Ready
But the stock exchange will remain
[music]
First of all, how about commenting on Som Distillery ji
Show the positive company's performance
He's quite good here on capacity expansion.
But there is an update that commercial production has started.
as well as metal counters
JSW Smitha All Metal Count Me
ICC foxes are already testing positive
You can also buy tomorrow option of 1140 here
I am of the opinion that the way the numbers have come is now fashionable.
Continuous week chart structure is
Let's go to Gwalior here too, Mahindra
And Mahindra is looking good for the long term.
Britannia remains the favourite among IPL stocks
Hai Accha FM GG Play Hai Jidest Life
Go positive by buying a science paper.
The news is here and the mic test category
I have a bike in M ​​entry but
You can buy in SBI and partner IGL
Opinion to do and the best pick among all these
Mahindra & Mahindra to launch 1400 units in next 1 year
that the target can show me that
Later on, TV Sher will become their Market Sher game.
You can see this happening in the same way as the SUV
See, there is a booking of 400.
Properties are looking good in the future
The features of the lines have to be sold because
The news is also good as per the options.
If you look at the options, you will get
Buy the put option of ONGC
Mannapuram Finance will be better
Fundamentally ICC proof is visible which
There is a good space for IPL stock.
According to him, Prestige Street Project which
He is also saying very well about the news.
According to him, Bachpan Enterprises where
Mike has increased his stake in this
Both Voltas and Blue Star if you look at
So you have news of Hitesh there.
Momentum may be visible as we come and finally
If you talk about GIC where Lombard
that the result is that there is benefit from it
And in all this my best fuga woh
Prestige Straight Project which G Peace
I have it, it is very good and the company's
The brand is also very good, so keep that in mind.
Prestige Straight Projects
[music]
Description below
So, you have a look at Milasa business.
This time we will see our markets
How to open the first vaccine on your screen
It has already happened and you will see a light red mark.
Sensex 500 will be seen down by fives
is settled on
If you see it, let's see it, a little scared
Where are the markets in the seconds before that
The rupee also appears to be starting to
If the commodity market is also being discussed then Deep
Just once before
I went over 82, now you're back together again.
If we have seen further weakness from then yesterday at 82 04
The band happened to be in decline today and
With the money down
Weakness is visible for the third consecutive day
You seem to be coming to the e-market
Although the toilet index was a little high last evening
Still weakness in the rupee this morning
Kutch oil will be seen in the opening session of the dairy
It is something bigger than the last two-three years.
The movie is not a light-hearted one
The collection came after that you are watching
The brand is trading below 85
You will see Ved trading at 8081
Natural gas is being produced here continuously for two years.
You are seeing positive action this morning.
It has started at the level of 194 but on this
Keep an eye on it, two days ago there was a huge fraud of 9%.
I saw you here, and gold is also a
It is in the range, there was a slight movement yesterday.
There is hockey-fueled buying in silver
Yesterday is the basement, there was definitely a rebound in it, but
No big action this morning at the opening.
A has been in both copper and aluminum
You seem a little divided
aluminum, by the way, if you look at
Two-month high in the international market
But if it is there then you can see the initial range
There is some weakness in the rupee but we will see.
Let's take a look at how it is worn today.
Top Ten of
[music]
ICC Lombard Salt year good growth
Profits were also seen and net
Premium and also which is much more than expected
Better is the net free, mother came up 12%
And see a 40% increase in profits.
Premium growth from the segment is quite strong
and 31% in the retail health vertical
There has also been an increase in the bank insurance channel
26% I look big here I am seen
He did most of the procedures on his own.
[ __ ] boobs are maintained from yesterday
Free targets adjusted but overall
Numbers looking strong are the top priority.
I made five to six questions exactly like Tata Coffee
The numbers here are not that good in fact.
The market expected a little
Better numbers will come whatever performance I get
Tata Coffee is up 10% today
Profit is 20% higher but working profit is 5%
Your margins have also come down.
Countries have reduced from 17 to 15%
Their operation in Vietnam is going well.
But coffee plantation business is also good.
But there is a lack of demand in Africa and the cost
The greater the impact on increasing profits, the better.
The profit is not as much as it could have been, so it is a little
Tata Communications is definitely facing cost pressure today.
The result will be presented but the result is already there.
The type had become weak the day before yesterday and was not working well.
The result is not expected to be revenue
There will be an increase of only 2%, there will be an increase of 2% in profits
Operating profits may decrease by 16% and
Margins are flat, meaning there is no change.
There are signs of this happening, that is, this time there is hope
Tata Communications does not exist
absolutely
The government has made changes in the tax against
So ONGC India MRPL Chennai
Keeping an eye on a company like Petrol
Increased taxes on domestic oil production
From zero to now 6400 per turn
Windfall tax will be applicable but on diesel
Export duty is currently completely waived.
If it removes it and makes it zero, then these are big changes.
Okay, so here are the instructions for you.
Interesting stalker now Reliance is here
Watch out for the vulnerable city of tomorrow and
The grams in Singapore that measure crude
Margin is made on the refined
He is 6 Meena's who have come to the stars
and are even under $3, maybe this is also a
This is the big reason why weakness was seen yesterday.
Reliance stock has excellent land assets
It's going to be listed today and tomorrow we'll list it.
Was also talking to BML last year
This was demarcated and now let's see where it is.
We will take action against those who copy the fair value.
270 to ₹300 depending on the calculation
Shipping Corporation has brought this tax per share.
Trade today and withdraw from the trade now
has moved into regular trading and
Its circuit limit, which was 5%, has now been increased to 20%.
will go and the reason for this is that when its land
When the business disease happened, after demerit
He should keep this for the first 10 minutes.
Does matter
Even today, if my asset remains the same then now that
The time is up and today this too
You will also get good news from them that
Their financial preparations are coming soon.
I also seemed to be trying to bring it to the end.
There is preparation from the government side and land too
The list will be out soon, anyway, I'll get this.
has gone
Keep an eye on metal stocks especially
Tomorrow you will find aluminum counters
You might remember that in the second half we had
Activity was also good, so Hindalco Vedanta
Tap here so you can see the action coming
Because aluminum is in the global market
The strength of has reached a two-month high
OK and meanwhile this comes from Gardner
Outlook 2023 for IT giants
He gave his growth forecast of 5.5%.
This calendar is retained for rail
And the most interesting thing is to see all
He is seeing growth across verticals
So in a desperate mood, Gardner turned to
The outlook that has come regarding the IT sector from
These IT companies are globally
Confidence booster and finally Evolo
Technology listings were sluggish yesterday, but
Goldman really benefits him in cheap
His friend Kims picked him up here around 8
India Equity also bought shares
Shopping is expensive and Mauritius is also affordable.
If you make a purchase, you are assured of golden sex.
Let's see how the plan will perform today.
Technology: This is today's top pick for you.
Ten Stock
[music]
Here are the top ten stocks for your retirement.
But now let's talk about some more stocks also.
Title Amritsar should be taken with experts
No, according to the demand they are getting
hai with wedding also I mean increasing aa
Gold Price by Decently Well and G Hisar
I think it's exactly
Positive what I think but I think that
Reliance Jewels Also Jumps in the Long Run
In fact, Vikram is quite aggressive, so he is the only one.
worry is adverwise n typing this til n
Good long term bike come here which is mine
The target is around 3150-3200.
Okay, so this is your title where you
Keeps an eye on you, have you also joined us?
We welcome them too, everything else is good
Morning sir I know your pic of D De
Good Morning Mera Pic Of De De Hoga Matlab
Puram Finance
I think the whole rounding bottom pattern
I am doing dung from here, I should go up to 140.
There is a view of both from
The band around 31 is the target of 140
should be
[music]
Bank Nifty's positive action filled
Let me know if there is a market.
So we won't do anything, Deepa, wait calmly.
We will see
17550 17625 First wine that comes out
If you enter this range first,
If it comes down, it first goes up to 17750
If in the range then profit booking there
Will review what is
Which is likely to go down a little bit first.
Below
Didn't return much either
Such a bullish market touches the level
It turns around as it does
I touch the level of the mirror and give it back to you.
When I got up from the table, I found out that the level had returned.
I missed it, it's not like that, everything is easy in Qatar
Everyone who comes will get a chance, slowly the line will
From
Rock your level 17550 17625
Not before you enter the range
I have to add 175 a little more to 700.
Booking some profit around 750
As far as 42 125 first entry is concerned
Points are made if you want to do it comfortably here
Bhi Watan Watch Dekhiye Mahal Iske Yaar Bell 125 Do
The entry point is
You have to take a little at a time, but more at the same time
If you don't want to take it, first go to 42 450 42 N 500 A
So if you want to book profit there then
Relax and wait for the level to be full.
Don't be hasty
go up first
ok sir so wait for the levels and
Then only you can tweet here people's opinion
You are seeing a cut on diesel at ONGC.
Export duty has been reduced on the butt route
Windfall tax has been paid back once
Trains on ONGC chart from Kunal ji
Kunal ji, a sub-station opened downstairs the day before yesterday.
Nifty's top loser will be at opening
Sir, please see the chart of ONGC.
Look at the chart structure.
In Deepanshu stock, we have continued
I have seen the software and today it definitely has some
You will see the collection coming in the beginning
in trade but I think the bottom
Good buying interest at the levels
If you want, then go for the stock around 155.
There is support, I don't think he can reach his level.
Should go down slightly weak below 1505
If it happens then in my opinion a little more weight
Watch for buying opportunities at lower levels
Better strategy in finding opportunities OK below
Look for buying opportunities at the level but ONGC
Come tomorrow take on this one more time
Rally with Vishwa ji, Vishu ji should go tomorrow second
Yesterday Tech was becoming very active in the half.
There was a good move, big capital is leading
was also the top gainer at opening today, opening up 1%
Is there any opinion about this the day after tomorrow?
Aa Deepanshu ji's statement is within the red range.
and the lower end of the range around a thousand and
Right now we are in the opening running around 100075
Immense and off range is around 1150 me
Looks like it is relative to other IT stocks.
regional placid and here perhaps if
There is a slight call-off after the opening
If I get up to 100060, I think
Should buy the same thing that was in Emphasis
Tomorrow it is at the support level of 2 days ago
Very nice candlestick patterns made me
Looks like this mouth can extend 1110
But call off should be purchased only till 1060
Date wood by n butter level too inter to 1060
Would be a good entry level and keep an eye on it
Today it's about C-Tech's performance and the rest of the IT
What kind of life am I becoming for you?
Looks good and prestige status is also good
He has opened a shop in Bengaluru.
The company has acquired more
He has 51% subsidy in Dashanya Tech Park.
This company has bought the share for Rs 66 crore.
These are commercial office construction and
Amritsar track does the development work
Do Prestige Seeds Recently Real
Great updates from State Complete
have come
It's hard for me to check the chart.
Sumit ji, please take the chart once.
See what Prestige status is all about.
Sir, there will be important levels for this.
It seems that in the last few days, one of the two is good.
The mouth has been seen inside the stock
In the middle, there was a support above the charge.
It has become close to ₹430 435, so this is
A shop will be built inside the lower level for ₹450.
After breaking the level, the momentum will build further and
Then the stock is trading at ₹465 to ₹470 levels.
can be seen above
Those who have made positions are in the hall
Training software
10 to 15 rupees worth of mouth and above
can get as you once Hindalco
A look at the price of aluminium
The handle is at its highest point of the month at the opening.
He is also the top gainer and the second biggest gainer is 435.
But how do you feel about Hindal, sir?
[music]
I have had enough of it, almost 400.
I've been here in the last six or eight years
There is a resistance of ₹440 so I will buy fresh
I will wait for the claim to clear ₹440
So here you will find a price around 440 in fact.
You should book bar profits
If it can be found again around 420 415
This is the profit booking level, okay, so this
There is a profit booking level and it comes on the light
Then you can take a look back here.
But let's see how the performance will be today
The handle should also rest on your side.
Shipping Corporation here also once Kunal
Let's discuss with him Kunal Ji Trade
You are regularly exiting the trade
Trading is going into a 5% circuit
The filter will now be 20%, 5%, 4%, and even higher.
Khulna is the impact of Shipping Corporation
Sir, please take a look at the chart
Watch Definitely Like Positive Impact
Dipanshu will affect the stock, we had seen that
The stock was consistently performing inside
But I think something from back
Traction will be created above 90 stock anyway
If the technical becomes strong then it will reach 90.
As long as the vaccine is given above, they will have it
I have a long position, just hold it and move on.
The next congestion appears on the chart at 105 106
So that seems possible on the service.
Okay, so this is Shipping Corporation for you.
You should keep an eye on the strength of this stock at this time.
The first tick will appear on your screen.
It's ready and we'll see what kind of
You can see the action unfolding in the market here.
It is visible today on the first ticket and
All Indians are signs of the very beginning
Any special action for you for the clouds?
18.2 is not visible at this time
completely
Even the sweet sound of the bell cannot be pronounced as bell.
Only this sound will come in your ears today
So
Sensex slumps eight points lower
Nifty is open at 20.2 Bank 50 is open at 20.2
So now it looks absolutely calm.
Now all three 10-20 indices will bring you down.
See the mark below 20 Nifty 35.nic
You will see it with a red mark
Indian initially and but not so
that there is a particular major weakness a little below
is 15 17 down between the green and red marks
I will see 50% off on stock.
Which ones are stronger
Top gainer Koyal India
Is
Hindalco Tata Steel Thodi Si Metal Showroom
You will see HDFC Bank one-fourth
The day after tomorrow, Magny is strong enough to make this move.
trying to do something special other than
There is no action in Mahindra and Mahindra
What should I say, I mean a little red green
If the mark is just right then the top gainer is Tata
Steel has grown by less than half a percent
What is weak is Infosys is weak by 1.5% and
Today's top news is apart from this one percent
Tata shares lose 1% on hike news
Consumer is weak, % of porn in Wipro
You will see losses in conjunction lions.
But today Fox is looking for weakness.
If yes, then perhaps these might be less for you.
Tata Consumer Nestle Lever Asia Paints
from all the stock of which earlier
Infosys, TCS, Kal Tech, these two spaces are weak.
are stronger in lions if you look
If you want, then these two spaces are Metal and Auto.
Listen carefully to Metal and Auto Hockey
Bank Hockey is showing signs of strength
indicating strength in that too if
If you need a sign of strength of charity,
Only metals show signs of weakness from IT
are and the conjunction is from FMCG intake
This is the initial trend for you, which is 3.5%.
You will see the loss in ICC Lombard
After the rivers, it appears to be weakening.
As of the day before yesterday, you will see below 1100
Biocon, here you will suffer 0% loss.
Infosys will also see a gain of around 1.5%.
Before the Tata Communications result tomorrow,
Its T was started and is still maintained at 1.5%
McDowell United weakens again by 1% today
You will see a loss of 1% in spirits
Force yesterday's stop which is 1% below the age
Today all these artists like Birla Soft etc.
Some profit booking was seen
But after the result ICC fox where
Broccoli G has cut most of the targets
This stock is weak and from 3:30
Now the woodcutter is cutting down below like this
Hero, I will tell you the complete update.
With the help of percents that will help you consistently get a lot
Looks like both here
But it has good strength. Top gear is habit 1%.
TVS Motor is up 1%
JSPL taps Hindustan Copper Vedanta
All the metal stocks you are looking at are
Insaan Mein To Aaj Star Performance And
Weakness again in the leadership of It Lion
2019 looks set to be a strong year
But in every person hitting a half century
He has been seen trading with great enthusiasm and
To bring Sensex and Nifty up as well
I'll try and you'll see
Does it have prestige status in the market?
Keep an eye on what they did with the land company.
Acquisition tax is ₹51% stake purchased
Its impact has been up by two and a half to three percent.
You can see glass rocks on this counter.
I see you in action
Because the price of soda ash which we will see yesterday
Were highlighting for Tata there
If there is a fall then C India Glass Italy Glass
Floor
You are seen in positive action.
Movements you also get in indigo paints
It seems to be a bit active yesterday too.
Only the ID post is showing active line today
Shopping in India is happening at Sheela Farm
Fortis Healthcare and
Both Narayan Vidyalayas are active.
In the big class of Narayan Vidyalaya, we are in the middle
I was also talking about Fine Organic.
There is also movement in Kims, another hospital stock.
Where you see PNC shopping
Infra Lakshmi and songs are also available here.
Positive momentum will reflect the result above React
Tata Coffee is also doing its business at this counter.
Keep an eye out for action here.
Shipping Corporation will remain where the circuit
Filter now back to your 20% T you T
The stock has come out of this with great speed
I see you at the counter
List of Land Assets in Nazar Thodi Dar
IPL Lock In on the Global Surface
50% of the amount which is to be opened after 30 days
You will see it unfolding today, the results will be out today.
Mystic is going to get security from this
These stocks of Alok Industries are also on the radar
Welspun Enterprises will remain at its previous level
I have been driving this car since half a day ago
Congratulations to Avalon Technology, this is the slowdown of tomorrow
The listing was done but the news is that
Goldman is true, there's a little pillow here.
Keep MRPL and Chennai Petrol on these also
Look at any changes that have occurred in the fact
Impact coming to you on these counters too
Some weakness may be seen in the stock here
This has been the third consecutive day on Brightcom
You have got a circuit installed which gives an average profit of 5%.
Engineering is weak today Balaji Amines
But here too, the weakness of the Create team is
India is all down one day before yesterday Indian
You see weakness in the bank.
Home First After yesterday's rise, today there was a slight increase in this
Teamly service is visible in the counter below
Yes, there is a cut in Tel India the day before yesterday.
Shipping is also showing some weakness to you.
The sun is about half a percent weaker, both NHC
Hydro Power You will find a little bit of Mazgaon here.
The action of the entire part is becoming completely flat.
This is business, sir, there is no action here.
30.nic is seen going up by 30 points
Bank Nifty and remained in this range
I see you moving
There is quiet business and this quiet business
Deep in the middle, a stock gets into big action
I am showing that Piramal Pharma is taking big action.
The stock has come in, there is some news for this also.
I've come to know about their US plant
There is news of clearance for Piramal Pharma
Every human being after both the big and the beginning
If I saw anyone else then the matter would slowly get relieved.
Sumit ji, please give your opinion on this once.
Pharma lion in action and news for it too
It's a little better today
Is it a one-day wonder or can it work?
A little mouth can
I can see a little bit of the face, but
I am not feeling any great speed
It will be made because there is a good fall
Pull back and bounce back within the stock
If there are signs then this will happen in school and
Inside bounce back from here and face 5-7
It can be seen ranging from ₹80 onwards
Up to ₹50, then act upwards
One can see a big one, some big one
Don't expect a rise from 80 right now.
Up to 85 can be seen
So this is for you Piramal Pharma where
You see the moment coming, up 7%
If this is a counter, it keeps an eye on you.
There is also a section where you can see the movement being divided.
Tata Steel Momentum is up 1%
Tata Steel rose in the second half
Tata Steel was also active, still some
Vishwas ji is showing hope for the movement.
Just watch Tata Steel in action.
Will there be a little more move or in this range?
Tata Steel is currently at 109
But Devanshi, this level is very
It means critical
10910 You can say this is John if
If we take it above this, we will see a face up to 116.
But when I look at its data
I have specially seen the option change and we
Almost You Know and Towards Expiry
You know it's in the quarter half so I feel like
Seems like a bit of a difficulty here.
It will happen because 110 will cost ₹2 crore 7 lakh tomorrow
If the open interest of the lion is then I think
What Happens in an Situation April 27
The expiry date is already April 20.
There is a way can also come in this, two crore lions
If there is a large open interest, I think
and two stocks are good attempting but
Heavy is the bill, it takes a lot of time if
Because of SMS we are in 200 110 tomorrow
If we give unwinding then in Surat we will get 116
Will see it going but the market is this leggings
Other triggers so I think 110 tomorrow writer
According to me, wooden should be avoided.
will try to break out
Will trap Long but he will be a writer tomorrow
Bill Have
Keep an eye on Tata Steel, a little metal
You can see the move Shakti Hindalco Tata Steel
Both are active in similar spaces.
You may also see some shopping in India.
The first one after the opening of the I
[music]
Keep a range of 50 paise with your stop below ₹2
I believe the loss should be below 82.
These 88 to 90 levels will be available to you today and tomorrow.
You can see okay so 88 to 90
Shop Target here
Some action has also come in metal stocks
Hindalco is also moving, let's see.
If action is taken against Vedanta or not
Because the price of aluminum is 2 months old.
The international market is currently at its peak
Havells has a great move
is being seen
Sir, he is the top gainer at this time, promise 2% up.
After breaking the 1240 level in Proper
The move from 1260 to 1275 is similar in Havells
can be seen in the week who
Position has been created, please refresh here
Shop the stops inside below.
Will be made in Havells around 1220-1225
If it is made then it will be done with a stoppage around 1220.
Buy at 1250-1260 levels
Can be seen immediately above
Hindustan Copper is another metal stock
Where you are seeing the move, Bansal ji, something
Time ago yours and Kunal ji's pick up d
I had also given it, come and see Hindustan Copper
The momentum is currently at the 10250 level.
Where will the stock go from here in futures?
Diwan ji, you have the technical structure.
If so, the opinion is to remain clear and
The technical pattern is good, it should be done
108 going towards 110 defined 100
Stock closes below Rs 10,000 and Hindustan
Copper buy opinion
You may see the move on Hindustan Copper
There is power in the tap as well as in the movement of Tata Steel
There has been action in NMDC as well as Vedanta
Now he is trying to come up, Anil ji
Keep an eye on metals, JSPL is up 1.5%
There is a space that is becoming a little active.
The time is actually complete here.
You have been watching the metal since this morning.
This is what we are talking about, metal is on the rise
And towards the market you have to focus it
But both themes will happen, you will see them increasing.
There are very few options ahead, join us.
Kothari is from Anand Rathi Security
Sir
[music]
I want to tell you this good morning sir which option
What is your opinion on trading today?
Good Morning
[music]
If the target is given then the bank
Nifty has come a little collective yesterday
In comparison, we are making that shift.
8 Today we will shift
42200 then
I want to take a put option of 42200 with stopper at 120
Whose target will be ₹50 and target will be ₹250
Anil ji, if you say so, then option of one stock also
I will give that too, okay, definitely
Why not, first the bank Nifty
I want to buy an option and I want to buy it at 42200
Bank Nifty is currently around 4200
The trade is tax and this is the expiry date of Kali
The option here is this put option in the index
Opinion to buy, now it is for Rs 150
Please provide stock specifications
If it can go up to 3788 then tomorrow's option of 85
This month it is trading at ₹1
I want to buy it, its stop loss will be 30
of money and my target will be ₹2.5
This is becoming a click-concessional option next year.
You can select the option in the middle of the mail.
We can create null commands like
Please also mention Regular Saheb in the features but
This is what I am doing, I bought an option of ₹1 for 85 yesterday.
I am getting the capacity to kill up to ₹250
And a little Moffly A power in the bank
If yes then it is advisable to buy the put at Rs 42,200.
Thank you for joining us, Mewal.
Sumit for sharing his calls and
Let's go to Zee, the super hit of Swagat
[music]
Tell me sir
There is a stock of Rs. The current price of the stock is
113 20 paise 113 25 paise is the name of the stock
NMDC has broken the highs of the last three
Opening the market inside the stock
The sector is witnessing an upset move as well
The top of the mouth is visible inside
From here, the upward move is definitely a full back.
It will be worth shopping here and leaving.
Stock which is below support and Shopclues
111 will be made, that is, a small stop loss
It is being made and the target that is visible above
NMDC may get its first target
The second target will be ₹116 and the second target will be ₹18.
of one to two for both or two to
Shop for three both for 111
For tags from Stoppage 116 118
Okay, so this is NMDC Metals for you.
Three calls from tax for you on metal only
She appears to have come
It looks absolutely perfect
The awesome metal is back in action and this
Even when the global market did not do so
Some big action is going on there.
Show but the action is taking place in a space
Fox does it on and she is of the houses
of sale
First earnings of 2023 i.e. from 1st March
From 1st January to 31st March this
Records of houses during the last 3 months
Breaking sales have taken place
Just understand the complete details of where, how and what.
We have all our desires with us, taking them all with us.
Sir, as the report is saying, if Q1
You talk about the calendar air, meaning from January.
Talk about March in 2023
Having a great sale
Species if you look at which Prestige
Check out the stock: Prestige DLF Oberoi
Reality Kalte Patil Microtek Developers and
Keeping you focused on all the real estate space
Now what is the data doing? What is the data doing?
that all of which are large cities in which
You have Chennai, Bengaluru, Hyderabad, Mr.
Pune NCR and Kolkata will be visible in all these
Why if you look at all seven regions
So the sales of your homes are quite good.
It was also seen to happen and according to them if you
If you see, you can see that record being made, Total
The units sold yesterday were 1.13 lakh units.
Whatever you have done in the last quarter, if you
If you talk about it, then almost if you see it
92000 which is a good selling unit.
Now if you look at the space region wise
So just the growth that has happened is the sales
If you talk about its growth, Chennai
You would have seen a growth of approximately 55% in
33% in Bengaluru 24% in Hyderabad MR
22% in Pune Around 30% in NCR
also 17% and if you look at Kolkata also
13% so one data is that and record
It is sold in all regions
Along with the new launches and new supplies
Even there you will have to go only if you are in Hyderabad.
If we leave aside this, then the launches there too
They also look great to you.
All six reasons can I give you good growth?
122% will be seen in NCERT
Growth that looks new while being new Lancers
Unit that came up is good in Chennai by 160%
40% in Bengaluru as well and beyond that MR
You will also see 2 to 5% in Pune and Kolkata.
If the supply that has come there is good then one
So the demand is huge along with this
which is new supply because if Outlook gives you
If it looks good then the new launches
I have seen him coming there as well and if you
If you look at the reports, some may suggest this also.
Although he is a bit of a leader, he is also
It's interesting that if you just
Talking about what is P investment
You got a pretty good cut there.
If you look at it, then there are three overall investments.
If you watch the series on demand, watch
And the new launches are great.
appeared to be
Perfect, this is the group for you.
You've been a big sales force, but strong.
Capital in figures
There is also a contribution which will be implemented from 1st April
If it is happening then now you will get it in the next quarter also.
I have to tell this to Ji in the same way in this sentence also.
Come on record
Firstly, still there is no doubt about the number
There is no one to boost your confidence
I definitely want to meet Jain Sahib.
Quickly, before the time is up
For Vishvesh ji, it should definitely happen.
special of
[music]
Anil ji
The name of the similar stock is NMDC now
Running cash came around 113 75
I think Sumit ji has tweeted this to me.
It seems that the momentum in the stock today
This is a five-day sideways move from the last car.
If today is continuous after moment
My view is a little bigger here.
Looks like a slightly bigger stop for 111.
If the lot size is large in futures, then here
110 tomorrow or 115 tomorrow later option
I think the first target will be 118 more.
The second target above that should be 122 and
According to this, you have no open interest here.
is made up
55 lakhs in 15 tomorrow I think date is this
n very heavy and open interest and there
Reminding is already expected if you
If you look at it, I think there are 2 lakh lions today.
Maybe this stock see you more than five days ago
If NMDC wants to pay less, then I will
I think up to 100 22 levels you're 3 to 4
You can expect it during the day, okay?
NMDC has 111 for you.
For
I
Time with Jain saheb also
[music]
MMT Industries Anil ji is a very
Good company, I would say I drank twice.
I have done it before and have achieved my target every time.
And the stock that has been corrected is MNP.
industries so now look when I last
If it was given once then on 1st June in June 2022
It means it was a day before your birthday.
And from there it went to the level of 230 and now
Correcting from there, this stock is down significantly.
Because Metal Jain sir, please mention the name once
tell me again
Or MNP Industries is the best company and
I've done it twice in James before.
And both times the targets have been achieved and this
The reason for doing it again is when the stock
Stay connected, see today your metal stocks moving
If so, this is also aluminum related.
Third largest company in products
Here you and its products are a little different type
and the best thing about the company is that
I think there are a lot of experienced promoters.
The company is operational since 1984 and has
Market share to make explosives
60% of the raw material that is supplied
The market is a share and the company has achieved a lot
Meaning related, he had done expansion
and collaborated Japanese type coffee
If all are there then look at the company aluminum and
These power paste and aluminum conductors
and is enclosed in aluminum foils and
Look at this product
aluminum powders and basically all of these
In them he is called explosive sorry
In all this
Meaning in Salary Explosives
Customers in construction and defense too
The base is also Indian Ordnance Factories Axle
Crop's solar industries, all these
And the companies in the cement sector
All these are also their
There are customers and about 5 manufacturing
There are units, meaning across Maharashtra.
Nagpur based on Maharashtra Metal
The powders are named so, meaning and
In shot form and aluminum foils
Also recently expanded the company name
So they are getting benefits from there also and
Japanese type as I talked about these three
Different types of taxes for different segments
And now I come to their fundamentals.
I was looking at the ratings, so the ratings
are also improving continuously and
When the company got connected, P multiple also
It had to be cheap, it is in the last and its
Later, this bounce from the bottom also did not happen.
Kia and multiple pay stop giveaway of 17
I think if the last 5 years
If we look at the profit, it is 17-18% of the sales.
17-18% and strong promoters
Share Holding Up and Price to Book Value
Not very expensive even in multiplexes
Stocks and I'm looking at quarterly results
Earlier the company was doing this tax of Rs. 3 crore.
There was such a committee and now this Continuous Five
Earning crores plus and
The December 2022 quarter was also good, so
If the TTM is around Rs 24-25 crore
If you look at the earnings of ₹20, the company does the best
Part of this is this even after all these things
There are not many dates in the books.
Equity rates are also generally metal based.
Companies and similar products
If I see it, I think this stock
can be taken at these levels and most
It is a good thing when it corrects from the level of 228.
If the stock is available at such a low price then it is a relief.
The target that I have right now is my target.
I want to give
OK, for the target of 170 you have to do
Shopping MNP Maharashtra Metal Powder
I also got to know its full name today, so here
I recommend buying it at
Well, we have come to know that after technical
You also do this and you also revealed it.
All the teams are looked after by RSI.
Let's see everything, pattern pattern
We also see a little bit but when
You
Fundamental research when you start out
Do you company names start with
what is its full name
I really enjoy looking at the name a little bit.
what happens to that
Look today, there are many meanings like MMT, so Maharashtra.
metal powder so they used metal powder
Reduced their five plants in Maharashtra
Yes, I also happened, then if their expansion
Relief, so they made it a short form.
Many times the name changes above, if someone coke this
If any changes come to the suit due to all this
Vision makes a huge difference, reveals
So I believe in the name a lot and
Ram has revealed that the mission of the man is done
With the button, like this Kunal ji
Rakesh ji has shortened his name like
RK Jat is called N, so what do you know from this?
has gone
The donkey is the same
Then in our Rajasthan also there is a very big
RK is a corporate group, so RK takes it when
This means what can I say, it is better than that.
No, these people both have popularity and this
People are doing amazing work, yes, popular
together
people who fall in love
So you feel from inside that no, I and
If I want to do better, I've seen how
And the thing about 2018 is that it benefited everyone.
Anil ji
Bansal ji I want to reply to you.
live by life
Mute
whenever such
wants
It was fun to watch me
Anil ji is the topper in between
People with 50% are also last
Venture to RK when Anil ji says it.
I have a very big feeling
To me it means that
He is a fan of G and is top in this too in Bollywood.
It is also top and South means Bollywood
There is LED there too top energy very
I got a good feeling when RK spoke.
If it is there then it is not small nor very big
He weighs a lot, he weighs a lot
nice wonderful very nice so this is your
For MNP this stock price Jain sahab
Glenmark news from this side behind a little above
I have just brought this face that I see when
People used to give you their opinion on Glenmark here
He made a settlement in America
Settlement in the case of generic drugs
And in that approximately Rs 5 crore 80 lakh
Fear is going to pay off
One click is quite negative and big
They are going to give the money after checking it.
For one drug, they have done it here.
Payment has been made
was not c
To reduce cholesterol
This medicine is used and has no
The case was with the well-known
They are a big international pharmaceutical company.
Her swallow was having an affair with him
How much did it cost to set up 5 crore rupees?
400 million
Will try but on de face of it
I understand that if 400 crores
If you want to give it to Glenmark then it will definitely work.
This money will not go into much money.
I will admit that this matter is a little loose.
It is written that please keep an eye on this stock.
Once again, rally from Amritsar will go to Fundamental and
After that Sumit ji took charge of Glenmark.
You be ready, I am coming to you too.
How is Amritsar looking at this?
D positive
So according to him it is a little negative but
Overall, I don't think it will crack.
because of this news
Tell me what levels are important for this
Inside stock in both the last 10 to 15
It's great to see you guys now.
No collections yet in stock
No signal received for the stock to move to higher levels
Trading is trailing shoppers for this
Inside he should
49495 495 You be very precious now 5056
The train is running at around 495 level.
Super has brought position hall up to 510
If the level is broken then the rally will increase further and below
If the level of 495 is broken then a good
Significant profit booking within Glenmark
If you have the strength, then set the train stopwatch for now.
You can hall 495 510 this is the range
Will remain in the range, if it increases above 510 then it will rise.
If it comes below 450 then the temple will remain closed for now.
Trade John type, let's see it
The formula was basically running which truck
It's been going on for so long, so long
And first of all, their agreement with Mock
Both these companies were taken to court.
Has gone
And this too and this is the first settlement, this is complete
The settlement has not happened, which I understand is a little
And perhaps there is still development to come.
Let's see what happened in the first step.
If there are any more details from the company
By removing this, the settlement is also complete.
did not happen
If it is there even after giving 400 crores then it means
will you rob
What are you doing even after seeing 400 crores?
To see if the settlement is not complete
It is interesting and this is 400 crores, I mean
Made a profit of about 2/3
This has been going on since 2010 This has been going on since 2010
Go to 2023 and give 400 crores in that too
The matter is still not fully settled after
And in that too, profit of two quarters
fly away
and divided by Varinder result less than one
[music]
Good Morning Version Welcome Tell Me
Which results are good on your radar?
Morning
Sir, I think it is important to tell you this.
that Goldman's numbers came out yesterday.
New York Milan's numbers came but one
The essential thing that GP Morgan City Bank has
And Wellspa has been a force in all of this.
Goldberg has a feeling that Sir is his
Do you remember that the deposits have not reduced so much?
would have self prices had become something and people
Who is afraid that all the retail people have all the money?
But at the list, these five-six will start coming out.
and the biggest among them is GP Morgan
It is very clear that the deposit is
The answers have not decreased as much as you know in that
And people were worried about Johnson Johnson's head
Double beat and outlook race of 43
means that it is going well in that there
But nothing is going too badly.
Where people were wondering what would happen.
There's a lot of concern about recession.
Like I said on the first day, Sir, what have I done?
Am Looking Global Republic Global Recovery
In what way is it happening
Little
Sir, only two came after the market was closed.
The numbers came from Tata Coffee and ICC Labak Tata.
Coffee will be very-very noble with your numbers
you know anyone
Break Communication Very Very Fine Other
line set of numbers so you know it was
Nothing Like Sort of Number Sales Flat D
Gross profit brother is around 45% tax
Till now ₹6 crore was Margins 15%
I heard from around that Sir, I asked him to speak in this.
For more honesty and an ICC
If it was longer, you would see more profit.
Because it generated higher investment income
and lower expansion fibers but their
Growth in freebies has slowed down a bit, but
Sir, this is more important than the result.
ICC's Lombard I think if your
It's nearby, we don't have that much traffic.
Or if you have it then there are two things in it sir, one
So this is going to be a sale of ICC Bank twenty
September 24th and this CEO has 10 air
And these two things are happening on March 24th.
which is Edwin and I've got country in it
There wasn't much good, so it was like this
Lamba again ok setup numbers but devar are you
important events you know I think both and
Looking at the list, this company has some
It wasn't much, sir.
ok so this is for you
So if you come then it's a matter of something less.
Tell me and
You have so much research in your bag.
There remains a little something else
Just to give you an example, there is a company
Which I personally like where
I wonder how come it's so cheap?
It could be like urine paper.
Market cap is around ₹850 crore or
He has around ₹800 crore.
The investment is worth Rs 450 crore, sir.
He has a land bank fixer value then
1200 crores is worth so many points you
What can you do with it, you know, you get ₹850
In crores you will get almost Rs 1600 crores.
Pics that are getting investment
A disabled group company is being found and if
You can see their numbers in management.
Joe is the new HD and CEO, Joe X
caption house kiya which means going ahead
You will see better numbers in the last
Look at the quarter number, my son.
I thought it was around 70 crores.
There were boilers band on their blast which
Karan Denial PowerPosh Gets Too Much
Compare you if a paper company that has been
If this generation continues in the future then it is expected
If this run rate remains then it will be Rs 250 crore.
The son of can do company sir and almost
Debt seat can make a profit because
You are getting this company four or five times
Plus I just said an you have so match you
Assets to this company as I told you
He has 15 to 16 such companies.
Ultratech happened, all their investments were lost.
Is
In a market where people think that
Nothing can happen
The company in Tera which you will get right now in Sir Market
Cap Joe is his cross batsman
The company is getting where people are going to get it.
If she is not studying then friend
Market is below cross market
is below the investment of and where
I am also seeing myself as rejected.
what are you trying to do in this tire
Environment
Side Butt in This Market Environment
Okay, so Orient Paper, this is a fundamental
Strong The best thing is that for the next 2 years
I have many such questions in stock.
which will show you some amazing action.
Thank you very much Samanna and Varinder
I will meet you again tomorrow to give you time.
Let's move forward and join us
Before that, a quick Google for specifics
There has always been a faith on their side
Specific
[music]
Tell me sir
There is a bus in Farmas Peace and a Pharmacy of Fino
The good thing about the stock is that
The current price is Rs 305.60 for cash.
level and I feel like the stock
It has come out with a very good consolidation.
After Gradual Decline, yesterday was the bag so
Here 302 means stock plus ₹3
You should buy these two at Rs 315 and Rs 320.
For Target, I think a
Should be purchased in granules
Around 302 means there will be a stop the day after tomorrow
I am feeling like this for the last six days
Consolidation is that website breakout.
Along with D Central
OK Bansal ji, questions are over.
See also on Tor and here the target is up to 320
What are you waiting for from Vishwesh ji
Welcome Siddhartha
[music]
Good morning, good morning, tell me sir, today in this
theme of the week
Good morning Anil ji, good morning
Deepanshu, good morning to everyone like Anil ji
You are always in charge, just like today.
The theme that your portfolio should also have
Need to keep charged up and it's electric
Vehicle theme: Switch to Electric Vehicle
And the name of the theme is Plug
And the name is Electric
Area to your portfolio which our
Crude oil on important oil
There is dependency, it must reduce
There is a need to reduce pollution worldwide
The mobility that electric vehicles offer
Usages today are 86% in Norway and 86% in Ireland
72% in China which is an emerging country
On the Indian side, 16% of that is India
37% will be charged on vehicles by 2030, which is 5% today.
It is giving full incentive for 2 minutes
to the consumer
to the manufacturer in terms of electric
Where vehicles can be better
Electric vehicles in overall non-metro
The team is doing very well as well.
if
This electric car is going to be launched at 49%
These are vehicles, these are passenger vehicles.
I think there's power to be even stronger
This is 1 lakh a year.
Bittu Wheeler Four Wheeler
I would have considered the compact to be 47,000 last air.
plug and
play hum hai ye
Your Perfect Electricals theme is today
Tailor made butt I Sir, which are the themes in this theme
Lions are fit, how much money do they have?
And how much power do you have?
Whatever question you
The answer is that there are tax companies and all four are different.
Two wheeler and four wheeler are from the sector.
With Chemicals and Auto Accelerators First
Company
Tata Motors, whose target you have to keep is 600
Keeping a stop loss of ₹400 and a position of 30%
15% of the evil sale goes against the total
If I talk about electric vehicles
Passenger vehicles have a market share of 85%
Tata Motors' next and number one
Electric vehicle is the vehicle in India today
GLR is also reducing substantially
Tata Motors intends to make death free
To be and I believe that free cash
Tata Motors is a great fit because of the flow
It seems the second company will be TVS Motors.
Wheeler's company in space, Target 1350
It cost ₹30 out of ₹100
His electric vehicle is a two-wheeler.
Scooter market has a market share of 14.5%
The brand has strong visibility of 24%
Further capacity expansion is worth Rs 750 crore.
I believe that revenue 24 20% then 26%
TVS is a company that is going from earning to
Motor
Third, that auto company became gold from N.
Blue Coffee 630 Apply ₹20 off ₹100
Prox
Yplan Revenue Comes Electric Vehicle
from Key Products
The order book is worth Rs 23,800 crore.
related to this
It does, I believe that
Last of 630 gold buses in the coming year
Company
Electrol is the company that forms the group.
The planning chemical is now the electrolyte which
It is a chemical, that is battery, if it is the best chemical
I believe that in this company
electrolytes c power so planning
chemical
Apply 20% for a target of 30%
There is power
and Co Green
The calculation in percentage is going to 110% sir
TVS Motor 30 Tata Motor 30 BMW
30 and New
of ₹110
[Laughter]
1875 1875
1875 Fix It Planning Chemical of 1875
Target and current price planning at 1620
We would have placed a hot board in front of you once.
Yes, you will get the idea of ​​New Neo G
Planning Chemicals is here for 1875 tax
The target is the same, Jai Thakur is also ready.
By taking the cash option, but before that we
I will start earning Rs 10
[music]
Do you trade in the stock market?
Isn't it true, every morning at 7:30 am on Zee Business
You will find everything that traders need every day.
Daily Cash Future Option Index is required
Technical picks on the strength of news lion and
Nothing for investors, right?
A great investment pick and a great one
Funda Pick means daily dose of trading every
Every Morning
[music]
Anil ji, a big one in Zinda Steel
Breakout is 580 just a little bit
That level of 584 moved by three to four rupees.
It is currently ₹589 but you will definitely get it for ₹58586
I can find it in the collection here
Take it and add it there, I mean this is 620
Can go up to 630 in the next two to three days
Your stock loss is below 578
Should be mild and target from ₹620
630 time frame two to three ok 620 630
Buy JSPL for your target
One opinion from Amritsar also from Sahib's side
I had to take the theme given by Siddharth ji.
Electric Optional and Gym Kar Stock
Sir, please tell me once about Tata Motors and the rest
from you on electrical related stocks
I want to get advice on which stock is good
Shopping where you see fit
would like to
[music]
Even there, my target is around
Because of 680
I am very positive there.
Exide ours because both lithium batteries
The facilities are quite big, so I came
Think This Is One Space
So this opinion is for you from Amritsar also.
Let's move forward on all these stocks that have come and
Let's start earning Rs. 10 and Rs. 10
At the beginning of the shortage, the first trumpet is victory
Join us by taking the cash option for
[music]
Good morning Jai welcome today
very good morning
[music]
The unit is A so it must be different.
It can be very good by doing Asif here
The camera is very good, yes it is energy efficient.
I have installed a setup which has a little bit of glad etc.
Even if it had come, how would they have removed it?
His knowledge is very big, his energy is the same thing.
Yes, there is power from PCR, Anil ji
He's made a few adjustments.
And the rest was not there, she became smart so this
The saree is shining
I still feel a little threatened by Ashish ji.
It seemed like denial
It's on the chair
You don't seem to be shining much these days
I feel that Anil ji, this is exactly what
Nothing is going on and I just told Bansal ji
It has been written or not, please check it.
Needed
Bansal will reveal all those stars very soon
This is a big flute of my life.
We will also step out of our cabin.
He will open a couple of tunnels in the office.
Immediately
Such direct A can
But it feels really good to be complemented
He looks shining, he has good butter.
Please tell me today's option for the complement
I want to buy a put option of 300 on Bank Nifty.
which is also trading at ₹200.18
I want to buy this energy, I am feeling like this
There was some profit booking in Bank Nifty.
A could
So we can also see levels up to 442.
Anil ji can be found in this and in this
Stop loss has to be placed, date can be placed
Date 102 is yesterday's low, keep it below this
I feel that with a stop loss of 102
Also if you want to buy this, Anoop Closing
Basis in fact you people will keep me like this
Whether or not the Pengu team is on the upswing
is clearly at a loss for tomorrow and
Until Tomorrow
Clear resistance in the range of 42300 500
means the flip side has the bottom support
Nifty Energy also has a price of Rs 42000.
Kahani na kahani is not supporting
If you look at the market Nifty B
17800 is a resistance in the 17700 range
There is a support around 17500 so sideways
You are negative, this trade is hurting me, Dil ji
Therefore it is advisable to buy put option because
I am feeling a little like this but it is here
is on the side
Okay, so some money recovery is power.
Buy recommendation: Buy this put at 42,300
This is from Jackie on 218 you will get this
Time it will get 346 and then larger of 442
Target is why you can buy it here now.
Mayuri has just come down below 42 200
Kothari saheb also when small option big earning
When he got it for Rs. 200, he deposited the balance of Rs. 200.
The putt was being bought by Jai for 42,300
Do it, it is happening, so let's do it a little
Profit encouragement came to you from the banks
It seems he has the power but he can earn even Rs 10.
Stocks come from our experts
Vishwa ji, that's why his stock of Rs 10 earnings
Vishwas ji please tell me sir
Deepanshu, from my side, who earns Rs 10
The stock is named Aarti Drugs now
Running around 431 and stock almost
No sideways for the last two-three years.
download
It had reached Rs 300 and loose, now this
The stock is quality stock and
Fundamentally the stock is good enough for me.
Looks good, it runs on 26kp
Over in Specialty Chemical Pharmaceutical
4000 crore in sector you know flavour
Its market cap is now the highest
The important thing that I am missing is
Market Cap to Sales Almost 1.6 Like this
Key Quality Company with an Very Good
Category of Management When You Know 1.6
times market cap you sales milti hai
And I am buying this stock for the short term.
I don't recommend it, I think
One should keep a holding of 3261 here
I would recommend a stoppage a little deeper
Because if there were market wallets
So the stock is down a bit around 30040
But I think this stock is currently at 430
running around 650 which should go up to
Conservatives will be very
Beautifully Downloaded Sloping Channel
Break out me guessing so me
Looks like a very good fundamental stock
Reasonable valuation and no technical issues as well
Supporting It's N Good Technophone
3261 Point of View Today on Drugs N
Medium Term Targets Aarti Gates Here
Connect you for three to six months
Shopping is here for you
Buy stock worth ₹340 from Vishwesh ji
Buy for target up to 650
Priceless land assets are all that will remain.
Here's a closer look at the Fox listings.
And after listing, the stock
Doing 275 and 275
same same
I think at 292
If you look from there
It is 299, so our guess was 270.
Listing is in the range of 300
But on BSC, the price is different on both sides.
Whatever the difference is, I don't know why it is there.
But from around 295 here one after another
thing on and around 273 is
NSC
Listing of stocks comes to you growing further
Two special guests are ready with
Welcome
[music]
Himanshu Gupta has joined us.
And Jain sahab is already associated
We were back again after a break.
Jain sahab generally takes commercial breaks.
Which one does what between commercial breaks?
Apart from this, the other break is the one
drink
Which one nowadays
[music]
Make a ji and take three stocks by making streets
Are there short term limits for this pay limit for you?
Do it original and long term or Himanshu ji
If there is momentum then this
There is space
If it has strong fundamentals
About 96% of the company's revenue is
Domestic is the profit of the last 5 years approximately
The market of Rs 8000 crore is above 86%
There is a cap and the company's business is on Aarushi of 21
I get to see that and I think
of
Was a good stock pick and now almost correct
and has reached around 3840 TVs.
And on technical parameters also the stock has seen a rise in the last 6
It would have consolidated a bit in 8 months
It has been seen where a decent price
And I got to see the time collection
It seems that if from here it is 6 to 8 months
If we look at it, this swag is back in a hurry.
To pick up momentum to show
Ready for ₹500 for the next six to eight months
Shopping at Junction Pal Pal for Target
It would be advisable to move ahead at the current level of 350.
There are around 350 320 accumulation zones.
and a closing below ₹300
Sujan here on a stock plus basis
I would like to come
It seems to you that
Great company and very good performance
In fact, I mean, in these levels
What should I say, I mean I am from a very low level.
I commented and it's a great pick.
In fact, I would say that Himanshu ji
Very good, tell them what they deserve
Kajaria Ceramics is the way we look at it
The demand and meaning of real estate
Overall, I think that
Home innovations, home renovations and all that.
Which is basically home renovation sorry in all this
The atmosphere that is developing now, I feel that
The story of what is and what is demanded in India
It is a great beneficiary of all those who
This is a building materials business.
and Kajaria Ceramics is one of them
company and it is the largest manufacturer
There is an option for ceramic and vitrified tiles.
D World 8 Largest in D World to is
See more of their methods in our portfolio.
These people now use plywood and laminates.
Also included are sanitary ware, tiles and
These people always like very big stars.
If Akshay Kumar is made the brand ambassador
These people have brought Ranveer Singh and him too.
Huge business infrastructure built
What is the market according to what has been done?
It seems very cheap because it is like India.
Market means building an infrastructure
By doing this, around 2000 dealers and your
so big
Meaning you should be present in the country and 17000
If I get a company for crores then I will be very happy.
It looks cheap and this saree in India
I am also a building materials company.
I have made a lot of comments one after the other and
All of these will do well and
If we talk about the fundamentals of the company
24-25 Return on Capital Employed is 19%
The return on equity is the dividend yield
That's great, what about the profits of the last 3 years?
Even if it is 17-18% of the order in December
It was natural that the result was weak because
There was a lot of pressure on margins, whatever these types of
There were companies of but now both the coming forward
This margin pressure is very high in
Will not be seen and the lion is in a holding pattern
Apart from the promoters, I again gave amazing
Holdings are around 42-43% meaning
Yes, if you do about 43%, then I
Think investing in stocks at all.
Should and this stock can go from these levels
Around 1270 1290 whatever recently
It is made for 1280 and is also very technical.
Stocks and fundamentals at good levels
have something to talk about
Okay, so here's the full action for you.
Comes at this hour and gents by your side
Do you like your mix?
The soil of India, the soil of the country, this one, this one
absolutely from all
[Laughter]
Exactly what today's strategic time out is all about.
I told you I have to do all this straight away
GIC
Let's move forward and be a little scared.
Deep is ready before you get your 2000 today.
If you are bringing the update of Commodity Mazar then first
Deep, please tell me once what it is and where it is.
Absolutely sir, keep an eye on the money for the third consecutive time.
The day is looking weak and you are losing money.
And now there is a slight decline and it is down by 9 paise.
If you see money today, then it is business.
Although a little cheaper in dollars than yesterday evening
It was there but today our rupee is looking weak.
But the good thing is that commodities are also a little cheaper.
At this time, Kutch oil will cost you around £20.
It is showing a decline of 6625 at this time.
Natural gas is being traded for two days.
After the boom, it is a bit hot at this time, but
The price rose sharply in two days.
You can trade natural gas at 194 right now.
You will see that the gold is absolutely flat, only ₹10
Trading down around 6500 here
But there is movement, silver is also flat at ₹30
Trading above 75000 at ₹275
After yesterday's rise, today copper and
Aluminium contains a small amount of copper (1/4%).
Below is your hockey drop in aluminum
You are seeing a slight decrease in zinc
When responsibility has come, then the base medal has to be used a little.
Mixed trend but advisory commodities
There is some very slow business going on in
Also the action is not made at this time and due to this
But we are also going to ask questions of Anil ji.
Why did we see heavy silence in Sony?
It fluctuated up to 61400 a few days ago
We also saw Sony near record highs.
Saw it while leaving but a little from there
A retracement occurred and was followed by a very
If it is stuck in a small range then 3 from both
Soni's stuck in a very healthy dare.
Where does this pressure come from in business and further
There will be a discussion on how the process will go in Sony.
Why peace big for the entire commodity pack
Can say that some peace has come
Peace for you
Is
But one thing you said was that the stock
Specific action will be taken by the stock exchange
[music]
The heart's opinion is that you have to buy the future, Deep.
That is Whirlpool's around Rs 1330
1329 to straighten Bulbul's future
1330 is the power to buy futures here
If you have an opinion then you have to invest Rs 1310
Look around, so I can tell you
Done, you have to give one, it is summer
Awesome and this time what you have talked about is a hit.
And these 15 days came out in the beginning of April.
It has dangerous sales last year
Compared to April this year, April
The sales of another fridge are 20 to 25
is above
and Karnataka in South India in particular
Tamil Nadu etc., these states are here
Dangerous sales are coming, as if one
Demand is very strong due to Hit Wav
Sales figures starting with Initial A
You will not believe that such a situation is happening.
It's becoming difficult to find inventory
There is a line for these vehicles.
Okay, the beginning of the season is generally summer season.
If the shortcomings are prepared in advance
This kind of hit continued for a few days and then it became clear.
That after a few days you will have to wait for these also
Karma pada shakti is like that of the wind
There has been a demand for A and the second thing is from where
If the trigger ever comes, first fear and desire
He was telling about the sales of new houses.
The record is
Online averages from one in every new home
There was a time when it felt like 10 years ago.
years ago when 15 years ago when we I don't know
When would I have been put in such a house by a man, then he
It used to be a luxury and then we were just that
We used to put it in the living room, let's come to the guests
So how about in the living room when there are guests?
should be
Then after the living room, a bedroom which
Started putting you master bedroom in it
Now the entire house is becoming centralized like this
In every room, in every room, you are like this
There is a lot of demand for Whirlpool in both spaces.
ACP is strong and
refrigerator
You can also keep Voltas.
The demand for such is very strong, you need to
The position should also be kept slightly buy
These two, 1355 and 1365, were from around 1310.
You should shop keeping a target in mind, okay?
Both Vile Tal and Voltas, if you ask
I have kept a little for this, do it for two
Keep a weekly view and do it from two
If you want to maintain a weekly view, then from here
5 to 10% upfront for both sides
You can play stocks
Both these stocks are good ones to buy.
should be kept
but rather the fundamental sales that are flooding in and
The songs that are sold now, like whatever house
also has
The interior will last
It has lasted for 2 years comfortably, depending on
Size so I think this is a great theme
which has to be played
Havells also had a Spice on opening
Well, that too at this time by making a promise with your mouth.
I was also the top gainer this morning when the opening
The session was done once in a while on a charge
I want to take advice on charging
No, Voltas and Willey should be understood once
Do this rhythm, any of you volunteers
If you want to do it, then I will tell someone else
I will ask Bansal ji to enter and reduce the cost.
I mean a lot
Bansal ji is always ready
Thank you tell me sir
He was in the living room remembering old memories.
how did it feel
Put a sheet over it
Not everyone was looking for themselves, Anil ji.
It is absolutely correct, this is the fact.
There is no question, but as per capita income increases
Your standard of living increases
There is luxury
And in that too there would be children like Bansal ji.
He was like that, I had to sit in front of him.
I will sit at this place where the fight is taking place.
There was also a fight for
You must have done all this
children were put on because today
Their compressor is less in extreme heat
If I stopped doing it, I would ask for water.
There were many times more
So a lot had to be done and Anil had a lot of
I am feeling good, just like Marylee Bottom
Anil ji is nearby near the bottom
Technical and below around 1300
It is a good base and like our Jain sahib today
Tomorrow 200 is enough for the moving average
If you are marketing then this stock is 200
Kisses the day's moving average of ₹1500
Will test the level of plus from next two
Within three months, the hole will be tight.
Voltas is also doing very well technically.
And in fact Kunal ji is also liking it.
For Chaat Corner as well as Voltas
Technical Relative Cooperative Strength
If we look at the parameters, Voltas gives this better
Whirlpool Butt N is inside both brother mode
Both can be made statements.
Voltas is technically superior to Whirlpool.
Looks strong both financially and fundamentally
Both make almost equal amount of these
They make refrigerators and both have big sales.
There is also a little more in South India
If sales are booming then Bulbul is taking advantage of it.
will increase more in northern India
If they are there then Voltas will get more profit everywhere.
This will happen, you can do it mother, this is good
I remembered that once I looked at all the panels
All the experts I spoke to asked about their experiences.
I want to know the life time experience that
Deep said Deepika, there will be no happiness.
There will also not be any
Who among you has repaired a punctured bicycle?
Is
And that's it
[Laughter]
do
[music]
After taking out the dumpling in water, that place
after giving him dust,
Apply the solution, stick it and then tear it again
so full of air
[Laughter]
give something
I will also explain the question.
[music]
Even today, if anyone has a bicycle, my friendship
Disco
Absolutely
Is there any trick of yours there?
Anil ji, you will get a bicycle there on credit.
What
No actually
Making Pankaj also means you should first look at it.
Watch all the films of our time
It is enough to get the most heroes and heroines
The heroine's car broke down
There was a heroine position caste in his making.
Okay, let's move on and now it's time.
Market Outlook for FY2024
[music]
One is joining the program till
Very special guest Mahesh Patil Sir is with us.
Aditya who is attending the program
Birla Sun Life Mutual Fund
Investment Officer and more than Rs 3 lakh crore
You manage more assets 30
Your tomorrow is longer and deeper than a year, people.
You are the market leader since 2005 Aditya Birla
are also associated with mutual funds and
Personally, you are also looking at many funds.
Well, if he is the CEO then he is the CEO of all his friends.
The responsibility is yours and the qualification is yours.
You know sir has sent an MMS.
from Jamunalal Bajaj Institute, Mumbai and
Fellow with a Bachelor's degree in Engineering
I graduated from Mumbai University
You are very welcome Sir, thank you very much.
Financial Air is the first to give time
This financial air has already begun
I want to know from you about the market
What is your view on this? What is your outlook?
Is
Hello ji good morning
The last air that was there is enough for the market
Flights were reported last week
Market story is there was a Range Gurjar
From here we are getting information that in the market right now
However, going forward, there will be some news growth.
I am having a bit of a problem
So many sectors are global gender sectors.
There's a bit of a disappointment there.
As we have seen in the IT sector
The result came and there was a little
Is it the banking sector or the capital goods sector?
It happened and what is there worries us so much
It is not visible there
It will be quite good and whatever the market
The valuation of the market was less than what it was a year ago.
The valuation was quite expensive compared to
The long marriage still lasts
There has been growth in the past two years and the market is there
If you've been there for quite a long time, Waluj
If the term is around the average range then the market
It's not that expensive from here either.
is in the realistic range and we believe that
From here, if the market returns come
The company should be around its area.
If we have power then we are losing it
If we look at Nifty, its app growth
It will cost you approximately in the range of 12 to 13%
You should get and
If there is growth there then
Market returns may also be around that.
Although there are global concerns right now
A little bit slower Dr. Uske Karan Newton
I probably market
Jagrut na de I mean this year's agar
Talking about the calendar, the next 6 months
If within then the market will probably remain range bound
But come here, the investors lens two-three
Investing from a yearly view
There is no market for us from here also.
Looking at dance though next year
Elections are around the corner and we have to keep a close watch on them.
How does that result in a stable government?
If it has come then the long term of the market
The outlook will remain the same
But if your view is 2 to 3 years then
It is a perfect market to invest money.
From today onwards, Sir, this Indian market is global.
Sir, what about last year regarding the market?
Competition: Performance slightly better there this year
There may be less chance of worries
The global market is also actually good this year.
If I look at the last three tax months
It has come up a lot from the bottom, especially China
Like the market or the one from the Asian market
There has been a good recovery there but I think
We are a little worried about the global market.
It is because there or especially on that side
Come to Europe and there, their global GDP is
Growth is going to come down significantly this year.
Because there were interesting hacks
and the liquid is not coming, that is enough
If there is a big mantra then its impact
You will see in the next few cottages so there
But the underlying growth of the company will be
She will be very weak, let's talk about her impact.
So there's this calendar
Yes, there is power and because of this we do not feel
that the global market can accelerate further from here.
Although the sentiment is still very weak
If it had happened then the market was above that level.
stay here
And but the fear that I was feeling about the earlier market
Whether the bottom has been reached or not, we are confused.
Key Market Global Market See Well Today
The Indian market has definitely bottomed out.
This is because the market was concerned
Taking inflation into account is quite a lot.
The impression is still quite high and
There is a possibility of slowing down and interest
Rhett Hicks is also there in that if you look at it
Inside there is another one rate hi ho power and
It is expected that the benefits and off
Calendar air: Interest rate cuts are likely
Intercity is not running right now
You are driving for some time and it will remain when
If inflation is completely under control by then
Global market I think relatively I think
If we look at the development
The result so far is visible from there
That again, like in the IT sector, there is a lot
There is a bit of fear in the mantra, by the way.
There was also concern that because of people
Tu strenght but n market ki expeditio
It will have an impact so soon, so whatever
The sector I talked about is global
Its link with growth is that you can see the IT sector
or exporters like have happened and semi
Commodities are the driving force for earnings growth
Respondent A is Shakti and Domestic
Specially consumer in the fencing sector
Discretionary sectors such as consumer
variables and retail there we need to know a little bit
Slow doctor is visible especially in the last
Prestige season was quite after Diwali
In big big mantras there and there
The results may be a little weak
We are seeing good results there.
You will find a lot of numbers here.
Hope it comes out fine
And where are you a little careful?
So we are positive banking
The sector has not done anything special in the last six months.
But in a month, I come and I get a lot of credit.
and the profit ability of banks
She is also very good at mantras.
The first year of Covid was much more than that.
Rained good bikes in big mantra
is good and valuations are also banking
Computers are not that expensive in this sector.
The financial sector is doing well from here.
other than that
Even in the capital goods sector, however, we
Still a private topic
Ketchup is not doing so heavily in the chanterelle
But if people write then what is India's
The investment cycle is losing us.
that from here they will
Although in the short term there is a pay pain
As you can see, there is a lot of stock there right now.
have corrected and in the long term we will
It has been said that India's per capita income
More premium magicians will grow from here.
This consumer will benefit from it
Discretionary sector vs long term
There is power for good growth
So this is a good opportunity to look at this sector.
It will be very good in the long term
So here we are, the positive and the negative.
Talking about the underwear oil and gas sector
We haven't seen anything particularly negative.
Where, as I said, global
In the fencing sector, metal etc.
There if that growth is really a little bit
There is a lot of caste written in the mantra, so there
There is some power
Alright, this is Sir Ka Sir action for you.
To buy and invest today
From today, banks, NBFCs, pharma, cement and
Specialty Chemicals Mahesh likes this more
Partner, a little global cycle, which sector metal
etc., be careful there.
Sure Maheshwar, thank you very much.
Always on the give-and-take and market outlook
Our country was attacked by snakes in detail.
Thank you very much Sir, I am growing
Nifty is up 18 points at 17640
Loss
Down but spending time around 4200
We will take a small break and after the break we will focus on it.
Himanshu ji has been waiting for a long time
And Jain sahab with his position and 10
Some of the best earning stocks for you too
A short break in preparation for arrival
Super Shakti paces
[music]
Makes the construction super strong
Best Showroom Award Winner by DC London
R R Agarwal
India 360 will be shown from Monday to Friday
at 56
Business Park
A wonderful and flawless journey
The number one market leader
The biggest name of trust but style
Absolutely, you should do it according to your experience and understanding.
Veterans also salute asana
[music]
Do you trade in the stock market?
Isn't it true, every morning at 7:30 am on Zee Business
You will get everything that traders need every day.
Daily Cash Future Option Index is required
Technical picks on the strength of news lion and
Nothing for investors, right?
A great investment pick and a great one
Funda Pick also means daily dose of trading
Every day at 7:30 am, take it only on business
In the Trader's Diary
India
A luxurious and flawless journey, the number one in the market
Leader
The biggest name of trust but style
Absolutely common man whose experience and understanding
Salute to the giants, only profits in easy language
That is why the country is run by C business.
Your trusted business for 16 years
News Channel Shri Business Your Benefit
Do you trade in the stock market?
Isn't it every morning?
from the storm of
from the whirlwind of elections
from the playful statements
by the web of rumours
Now you
A wonderful and flawless journey
The number one market leader
The biggest name of trust but style
Absolutely, you should do it according to your experience and understanding.
Veterans also salute asana
[music]
Placement pick also
Showing
and some positions
Sumit's superhit for
[music]
Selling Stock
I'm seeing a little bit of pressure
Stop price is also running at 890 2893 stock
The name of ICC Bank is ICC Bank
Inside, from the level above the last two
Celebrations were seen even today.
pressure is being felt from the level and
It has happened to the people of both the last two.
Inside the stock, here you can do the walk
The time will be 905 within this, above I
Topless will become the bottom inside 884 first.
The target will be 884 in futures.
Trading for a move up to 875 after breaking the level
In terms of this, one or two can be seen in both
could
Up to ₹75 level down in such bank
You can see OK ICC Bank
Sell ​​here with a stop at ₹905
You should take these two targets along with you: 884 and 875.
At this time, I did some middleman on the banks.
Jet's opinion is also a bit scared of the first mail.
Ko Dhari Saheb also put his bet on Bank Nifty
The option was recommended for purchase at Rs 42,200.
K also tried to buy the photo option for Rs 4200.
Sumit ji had given his opinion on ICC Bank.
Here are some pics for you
Himanshu ji, please tell me about your position sir.
After Junction Pal Pharma
But Anil ji people like the stock.
Equipment for making compressors
is in business
I have commented earlier that it is a very good business.
Aarushi, who is 17-18 years old, does 120 company
The company's business is spread across countries
and cross sector cross industry company
Completing a collection cycle after
It is being observed and
Talking sequence here I think that
My stock appears to be resuming
Mother is that this stock is coming in both
back to back performance
If you want to keep the potential to show then 550 more
For a position target of 580 which is mine
I believe that in the next two to three months
You can see it coming in this stock
Shop Current
on the level and animals
Nearby Deep Any fall found up to 475 470
Advice to add more positions there
The stock will remain on the losing side below 460
Ka Chloe Singh Ka Kar Log Equipments Mary
Positional buying advice from
Elgin Equipment is the stock where
Positional buying advice is for you.
You should take two targets like 550 and 580 and move ahead with this.
Jain saheb please tell me about the stock, sir yours too
After Post Pay Kajaria Ceramics
Savita Technology and this company is also amazing
Fundamentals is a company and split happened
Recently I bought this stock twice.
James also did it and achieved the target.
Yes, and the company means you see zero debt
The company is offering payment multiples of eight.
The best thing I found was this and a very
The company is quite old and is operational since 1961.
and specialty petroleum products
It is formed like royals in transfer
White Owls Inka Accept Bol Ke A
If the brand is popular then coolant etc. is made.
Company and huge retail infrastructure
They also have a market share of around 35%.
Lion of the company and now I come to their
He also did Bhai Bag recently.
The company has invested Rs 21 crore in the
Connection has also come in stock and there is another region
Look at all these stocks of raw material.
Price due to crude oil prices
I was also corrected but I was not able to do so from this segment.
I have also used Panama petrol before, Castrol
He also did this and Savita Oil Technology did this.
I'll go into the basics a little bit.
I will tell you further, give a pawn on a multiple of eight.
Dividend of 30% is a return on
Capital Employed has a return of 21% on
Equity is of zero debt company promoters
Strong Lion Holding Profit Key Changer
31 32% Just Date's Quarterly Results
December ones were a little lighter because
There was margin pressure, so the stock was down.
It is available but such fundamentals mean every
The best way I've seen
I am in a stock, that stock is visible in this
Promoters have strong share holding
7172% plus then
If you sell around 9% then this saree
I've seen things plus credit
I have seen the ratings and they are also very strong.
So, after all these things, I feel
That this stock should be bought comfortably here
Target 330-340 with stop at 259
Is
Target 330 340 Buy 259
Stock plus all so oil this is your gents
position
A trading tomorrow is coming towards Jai Thakkar
Exactly for them
[music]
Tell
Absolutely Deepanshu Deepanshu see overall if
If you see, there is a good performance in metal stocks today.
Momentum has built as we meet and see special
If you look at it then Nifty Metal
The index is giving further break above ₹5800
I think it is heading towards
Level of 6000 50 Metal Index and me
If you like NMDC then the future of NMDC
My advice for buying is here
Clearly, if you look at the early charts
So this stock in an upper spoke in channel
Creating good volume here
Daily charges are being seen being made on
But if you look at it, it's very nice.
There is a download shopping train line Gaya Rekov
So on the higher side, in the range of 114 11450 you
Buy NMDC Features here
Only one single used to come after taking out the target
I will give it in Target and it is for Rs 120.
Its support on the lower side is immediate
On business it is 11250 now see for ₹2
With the stop loss above I upset you
Potential is about 5 to 5:30 so a good one
1:23 More trades are being made in NMDC
MDC is coming today, third tomorrow at this counter
Ji started early in the morning and after that
It was Vishwas ji's choice, now Jai also likes it.
Counter choice is being
Actually this is not there, today there are shortcuts.
Everyone is liking it so I will sell it.
Maybe everyone is ready to do it
Because the tap is to be tapped by NMDC.
Which bike is it but today really
is strong
All the metal is very strong
And she has come to solve the pending global IT
taking
Kushal Gupta has brought some special things.
tell me good
Sir, in this webinar two companies of the company
This webinar was conducted by an analyst.
Went here yesterday and it was the most interesting thing.
It came out that 10 days ago
They put global IT spend at 5.5%.
had produced the growth of
If they have maintained it then for the future
Here's the Growth Trajectory 2023
Kind of management country came good
for Indian IT companies in that
It is a big concern for them, that is not as big now.
There is no concern from their side.
That is to say, the microeconomics
Advants are those who are very concerned about IT spending
Will not have much impact now 2023
Now if we talk about overall spending
Here hospital health care health and
Life Insurance Manufacturing and
Expenditure in the banking verticals
IT spending is expected to continue
Whatever is strong will remain so because here
Irrespective of you if you are in cloud space
If you look there is growth intact and further
This is also a relatively better site for
On the other hand, it is estimated that
Joe ERP and Consulting over Austin.
This is the segment where growth is expected now.
Hopefully, that is, the enterprise IT
Vertical is the biggest Fox 2030 there is.
If it is going to be built then there is a need for vendor consolidation.
Benefits will also be available in future but the growth rate
He has maintained it
The important thing is this uncertainty.
Even in the midst of that, this growth if the gardener
is maintaining, it may be that a
There are indications that if it is taken from their side
If there is a prediction then it is your turn to star.
There may also be buying opportunities, but again
This is a dance, this is a company's view.
Maybe the rest of the people would have been dupers here.
appeared to be
He maintained confidence on Gardner's behalf.
There is guidance on tax, but this time there is a surprise.
But after tomorrow's recovery, let's see it
Sir, you have kept time for both sides too.
Mother is taking one earning of I 10 on this
Rakesh ji, his stock is with Kunal ji.
Tell me which strokes you have brought only
For earning 10
Moving ahead on the screen, today we
We are living again on an income of Rs 10.
Chemical and
Make purchases on chemicals and pharma
Earlier also I and Rakesh ji have discussed this
Stock was purchased earlier on the company
Seeing tremendous growth and out performance
We feel that we are getting our full
The group has not yet received this stock.
If it performs and will continue to do so in the future, then the current
Shop it for the fall on the stars
So stop will create new records overthrow Rakesh
Deepanshu has excellent technical structure
Collection is not listed in stock
Whenever corrections have occurred in the market
This is a collection, buy it for ₹2500
Our target is to sell it for Rs 2500.
Accumulate on decline OK Cumulated
Karen Ji Chemicals Sher Aaya Aai Aai for You
Time for short term picks
Yes Singh ji, buy for short term
The infrastructure is written, the current level of which is approximately
Very strong around 280 282
Fundamentally, it is a company which is basically a pipe
Oil and gas are in the business of saving lines.
In Kinarge and Wedges for Sector
Almstry Company which has experience of last 5 years
GR of profit is approximately 47% of 35%
return on capital
Very good on employees and technical charts
Breaking out a great accumulation session
Back by Strong
Volume is my society that this stock is short
Seen picking up a lot of momentum in the term
A could and new Joe Time Highs and 52 Weeks
Hi, some of the people coming here are made in both
If you look at the two variants of 330 and 350, then
Infra was written for short term targets
It would be advisable to go after purchasing ₹260
A top loss on a closing basis below
can be put on and go
Mangalam Cement Again a cement company and
In whose elder you always call me my in-laws
I definitely remind you of them right there.
There is a plant called Modak near Kota.
The place is and is a Birla Group company.
I would say the best company, the valuation is cheap.
This is the meaning of the best and plus the company
Congratulations on your recent capacities.
So the company has a capacity of 10 million tonnes.
And the company is being acquired for ₹763 crores and
The company's performance would have been even better now.
going on the last few quarters and
The December quarter was expected to be light.
It has to happen but overall the company has started doing
very well and I feel like more please
If 100% of the profit of last 3 years
has been around is a multiple of 19 and cement
The stock performed very well yesterday as well.
This stock is currently trading well above the level of 4002.
Correct Hogi is available in 280 levels
So dat is de best think and your moving
You should trade slowly above the average.
If started then I think the stock
305 310 for the very short term
Target and stock of 265
Where to buy in the short term
An income of Rs 10 has been lost from Jain Saheb's side.
Jai Jet Thakkar, tell me about your earnings of Rs 10
stock
Exactly what I get in Deep 10 earnings stock
like that's u know green panel if you
If you look at it, this is clearly a good stock.
Special base form has happened, I think this lake
Nice inverse pattern is forming
The stock is trading in the range of 28485
Slide 255 of this buy it below 2004
But if you put on Star Plus then exactly
Your Dr. Side Risk is 30 points
Here on the butt aside potential that Deepika is
My first target will be 350
The second one will give you Rs 375, so you will see after this.
Very nice a good pattern form
And this base pattern loses a little volume.
I am also moving forward, it looks very good.
Positive Divorce has been around for quite some time.
Daily charges are as follows and weekly charges are as follows:
The indicators have also given a Balia cross over.
I think looking at all of this is a bounce
Back stock can give from this level
A trade that earned 10% yesterday
From Vishwesh ji, of course for him too
Vishwesh's special
[music]
Bank Nifty is going weak, Deepanshu Bank
Nifty 42000 put option is around 8990
Available around 20 April
I have to pay the expiry amount tomorrow.
Looks like there is a lot of interest in Bank Nifty here.
Shaft can collect 36400 points
So you have to buy Bank Nifty put for Rs 42000.
Some lamps are available for around ₹90
I think it will cost around 40 rupees. 160
And the target of Bank Nifty will be 200.
42000 option is ok for bank nifty
Third right to buy put option
I am an expert in them
Vishwesh ji also has a short position in the bank
There is an opportunity to make the market cool today.
A significant recovery also came from a particular morning.
Slowing down slowly
Nifty has not fallen a little bit.
and in his place
Slowly slowly starting to go down
Show your current trend by doing this.
Good right for
It's time to take it all in. Thank you everyone first.
We would like to give Kunal ji, Rakesh ji
Many thanks to Himanshu ji and Sumit ji
Thank you V Agle Sir Vishwesh ji Jain
Sir and also of friend Jai Thakur Sir
Thank you so much Raja for supporting us.
Nifty is down 25 points and Nifty is down 100 points
Just Sensex
55 points
No, that's why Future has a big business.
There was some good action in the second half.
Whether it is there or not, we will do the show of the country
You stand in a place of respect
[music]
And India 360 will be shown Monday to Friday.
756 PM
Business Bar
A wonderful and flawless journey
The number one market leader
The biggest name of trust but style
Absolutely common man whose experience and understanding
Even the giants salute in easy language only profits
That is why the country is run by C business.
Your trusted business for 16 years
News Channel
Your advantage
Do you trade in the stock market?
by the storm of news
from the maelstrom of information
from the playful statements
by the web of rumours
Now you will get out
P and India 360 will be shown from Monday
Friday
at 56
on business
A wonderful and flawless journey
The number one market leader
The biggest name of trust but style
Absolutely, you should do it according to your experience and understanding.
Giants salute asanas
[music]
Do you trade in the stock market?
Isn't it true, every morning at 7:30 am on Zee Business
You will get everything that traders need every day.
Daily Cash Future Option Index is required
Technical pics on the strength of news lion and
Nothing for investors, right?
A great investment pick and a great one
Funda Pick also means daily dose of trading
Get on Business every day at 7:30 am
Only in Trader's Diary
India will show 3606
A luxurious and flawless journey, the number one in the market
Leader
The biggest name of trust but style
Absolutely common man whose experience and understanding
Even the giants salute in easy language only profits
That is why the country is run by C business.
Your trusted business for 16 years
News Channel Zee Business Your Benefit
Do you trade in the stock market?
Isn't it every morning?
[music]
So for the third consecutive day due to global signals
The Nifty traded near 17650 with the market pressure.
Near flat ITFMCG lions made
Pressure
[music]
Dead Song Special from the Heights of Dibeng Forest
SBI IndusInd ICC near tax 42 200
Bandhan Bank had established
Nifty IIT Index 7 from the fourth week
Infosys is on the star of the month list tomorrow.
Technical Top Loss
[music]
Selling heavy among FMCG stocks: ITC
Britannia Nestle Actual Tata Consumer
more than the decline in America
[music]
ICC Lombard Tax Percentage After Result
Tata Communications broke down today due to results
For the first third consecutive day, you
[music]
But
Included in the top gainers
up 3.5%
[music]
TVS Motor Max Health Prestige N
State of Sonata Software
[music]
In the final stages with a great response
DP Bank's investment reached at the end of
CBI asked for bids till the news of death
5% increase in NMDC Scheme Plant
Wedding possible in a month for you too
Exclusive business news
[music]
and the government's decision to increase capital gains tax.
No scheme issued in the Income Tax Department
environment focused on cleanliness
[music]
Hello, welcome to all of you on social media.
Special segment of 11:00 pm Ladies Special
I am with you Neha, a show where
Bazaar Today questions from female viewers
We provide answers to your questions before
We will introduce you to today's exports.
Reason: What kind of update is there on the market right now?
If he had placed it in front of you, it would have been the third consecutive
Trading Session We are looking at the product
There is some pressure in the market.
However, Nifty crossed the level of 17600 here.
But if you have done hall out then it is of 19-20 marks.
A hockey-like decline is visible there 42 200
Nifty Bank is close to 70 runs at this time
Showing a little pressure down and reducing it
visible and where the pressure is created
Actually we are looking at the IT space which is
The pressure from his side is increasing a little.
Impact Nifty IT Index also visible
will take on your screen which is 7 months old
Nikle Star has given birth to a boy, Infi Kal Tech
It is among the top Nifty losers today.
If so, yesterday we saw that some
There was definitely strength in selected pockets
Some companies are also in the top channel of Nifty
But nowadays the tech of tomorrow
We had a good performer here today.
I saw the pressure being released, but the pressure was only
You are not just from the IT space, you are from FMCG.
Go to the lions and take it to the index.
If you go, this will also create pressure on the market today.
Primary ITC has been reduced by Rs.
ITC as we saw it in the beginning
Here, parts of the historical high 400 come out
When I saw it happening, ITC called there.
I have seen it off-screen, besides this
Britannia Nestle Actual Tata Consumer
You can tell me from all of this that we
Watch the decline form from the upper heads but
Where are you getting cheap support from?
We have also seen in the market that metal
There is space here to offer some support.
Nifty Metal Index is currently declining
Trading with a strength of 1%
We've seen a little bit of support
It has also been seen coming from the auto space.
Underline if metal space is seen i.e.
To see the long metal of China
You see, yesterday we had a great event here.
I saw the performance, why is this so?
China's GDP figures are much higher than expected
It was better that he came because he was very weak.
There is some demand for metal in
Revival prospects divided, good
Although we saw that today only one dare
Trade appears to be taking place and this
But the momentum that we have here is from Karan.
The sentiment is that of a slightly positive boy.
If we are together then this is the reason why we have created metal space
Some good special attractions are being made from
See the list of Nifty gainers for you
Bajaj Auto puts forward its speed quite high.
Looks great, very close to 4500
This stock has a strength of two percent there
DBZ Lab is good, yesterday also we visited here
I've seen a great performance in fact recently
In 2018, we saw that the pharma healthcare space
Very good performance from the side for several weeks
Raha DBS Labs has led this rally
Yesterday also the band was formed with strength and today also
Strength has continued for 3:30 hours.
We are seeing strength of around 2%
But like I was a while ago
Metal space and specifically steel here
We have developed very good strength
Steel Tata Steel, we have done very well in this
When I saw the demonstration happening, what about you
It is possible that there is a lot of trade in just one camp.
A little dare is not much of a weakness
We are seeing Nifty trades being made.
Banks still near their critical levels
Halling myself out so this d
How with Nifty Now what do you get from here
We will talk about this today as the strategy is not ours.
Let me introduce you to the experts
Nirmal baki swami ji is with us
Swamiji has joined, good morning
You are most welcome, please tell me about Nifty quickly.
What is the weekly opinion on Bank Nifty?
before expiry
If you talk about it, then definitely we have seen it.
Test drive us today in Reebok
The opening from the side has been quite sideways
moment I feel upside down until this
Can't clear level 700
As long as there is that hall, as long as we
can keep
If we talk about Bank 50, then Bank Nifty
Little beat is compared to de neft